2096	"Trainning for Hero% has been completed."
2098	"My lord, your level has been to %d!"
2110	"Need User level %d"
2113	"Your other player is on on-line, so you cannot make attack."
2114	"Under the attack.  Please, wait."
2117	"There was an attack from our enemy while your absence, my lord!. Check defense record!"
2122	"Someone is on battle."
2123	"If you want to Guildraid then you have to be a member of Guild."
2124	"On battle"
2125	"Start to attack."
2127	"Death"
2128	"Challenge is available for one time only."
2129	"Now [%s] function is available to use."
2130	"Laboratory"
2131	"Catholic church"
2132	"Hero's Lodging"
2134	"Barracks"
2135	"Embassy"
2140	"Found %s"
2141	"Now [%s] unit is available to use."
2142	"Muat open the %s zone first."
2144	"New type of soldier is available to use."
2145	"Need %s."
2146	"Best"
2147	"Legion"
2150	"Freedom League Fugitive"
2154	"Advent unit"
2155	"Used all numbers of today's challenge."
2156	"Cannot make challenge any more."
2157	"It is locked."
2159	"Promote or summon %s Hero by collecting Soul-stone."
2160	"Need level %d."
2205	"Completed"
2206	"Comandable unit"
2207	"The League manager lady is my mother."
2208	"Hey! why don't you hurry up on your business and get out of here?"
2210	"League point is short"
2212	"Resource compensation"
2213	"Scouting"
2214	"Collecting"
2215	"Exchanging"
2216	"Advent"
2218	"Destroy"
2219	"Quest place"
2220	"Must complete the [%s]Quest first."
2221	"Must complete the [%s]Quest first, but the mission has not been received yet."
2222	"Acquired Item"
2223	"Acquired Resource"
2224	"No Acquired Item"
2225	"Reward has been received already."
2226	"Failed to communicate. If the problem is occured continuely, please turn off the App and re-start it."
2227	"Used all numbers of today's challenge."
10116	"Trader"
10117	"Guild Manager"
10118	"Robin"
10119	"Glaaki"
10120	"Arthus"
10121	"Toad"
15065	"Avalon"
15066	"Archer Troops"
15070	"Empire Army"
15085	"Savage tribe stronghold"
15088	"Hero's Lodging"
15090	"Savage marauder"
15091	"Assassin"
15092	"Savage tribe chieftain"
15094	"Empire punitive expedition"
25069	"Searching Medius Flatland"
25070	"Searching Medius Mountains"
25071	"Searching Medius Boundary Area"
25072	"Searching Medius Riverside"
25073	"Searching Medius Lake"
25114	"Plundering Sulfur"
25115	"Collecting Sulfur"
25116	"Savage tribe at Sulfur Zone"
25121	"Request accomplished"
25158	"Attacking Castle"
25179	"Seizing Frepugienchi Mine"
25215	"Seizing Mandrake Field"
25256	"Seizing Mine"
25307	"Searching Laboratory"
25308	"Finding Market place"
25309	"Finding Hero's Lodging"
25311	"FInding Soldiers' Assembled area"
25312	"Finding Embassy"
25313	"Finding Training camp"
25314	"Finding Catholic church"
25315	"Destroying Empire Archer troops"
25316	"Researching Unit character"
25317	"Unlocking Unit Blaze Knightage"
25318	"Visiting Market place"
25319	"Hiring Hero"
25320	"Training for Hero's skill"
25321	"Training for Hero's Command ability of Legion."
25322	"Joining Federation"
25323	"Upgrading Hero level"
25327	"Mounting Equipment"
25328	"Visiting Arms Dealer"
25329	"Selling Goods"
25331	"Purchasing Equipment"
25332	"Exterminating Savage marauder"
25333	"Visiting Barracks"
25335	"Exterminating Savage tribe chieftain"
25336	"Organizing Legion"
25337	"Recruiting Knight"
25338	"Visiting Laboratory"
25339	"Discovering Enemy Monarch"
25341	"Conquered Castle"
25342	"Searching Main Road area"
25356	"The first call"
25379	"New Monster Soldier is needed to use various tactics during the battle.  Open the 12 area zone and unlock the new unit soldier."
27069	"Search the Medius Flatland."
27070	"Search the Medius Mountains."
27071	"Search the Medius Boundary Area."
27072	"Search the Medius Riverside."
27073	"Search the Medius Lake."
27114	"Exterminate the Sulfur Transportation Unit who is pludering Sulfur at Contigs Riverside area"
27115	"Collect Sulfur."
27158	"Attack the Castle of the other lord."
27179	"Seize the Frepugienchi Maine."
27207	"Collect Steel"
27208	"Collect Mandrake"
27224	"Collect Gemstone"
27256	"Seize the Mine"
27257	"Destroy the Empire Troops who exists on the map."
27259	"Collect Sulfur."
27303	"Collect all resources for 100,000 each."
27306	"First, the Savage tribe around our Castle is threatened to us. Scout the Savage tribe."
27307	"Find Unit Laboratory to improve the ability of our troops."
27308	"Need Market place to exchange from all resources to Gold coins. Explore Market place area"
27309	"It is time to gather the fine Heros. Find the lodging in this area where many heros are gethered"
27311	"Need Soldiers' Assembled Area to improve the Hero's command ability for Soldiers. Search the Soldiers' Assembled Area at the Medius Flatland"
27312	"Lord's power is not enough to fight against the Empire. Make alliance with other monarch and gather more power. Need to find the Embassy in the Medius Mountains."
27313	"Need the place to train the Heros. Find Training Center."
27314	"Need the Knight troops to kill the archers in the enemy's rear area quickly. Find the Catholic church in the Medius Valley."
27315	"Empire's Archer troops is threatening the surrounding area. Destroy them."
27316	"Need to develop the ability of Arcane Archers. Press Laboratory Menu and study the one character of Arcane Archer."
27317	"Need the Knight Unit with fast speed to kill the archers in the enemy's rear area quickly. Unlock to use the Knight Unit."
27318	"You need to sell resources through Trader to get the Gold Coins. Visit Trader in the Market place and trade resources."
27319	"We need fine talented persons. Visit the Hero's Lodging and hire a Hero."
27320	"Without appropriate training, the fine talented person's ability cannot be shown.  Improve skill ability by providing jewel to a Hero."
27322	"There are many monarchs from different castles who have same vision as lord. Find them and make Federation or join their Federation."
27323	"Hero's level is increased through the battle experiences. But the experience also can be acquired by book. Provide the book to the Hero and increase the experience level."
27326	"Start the Troop command ability training."
27327	"Acquired our first weapon. Now let's equip the weapon to the Hero."
27328	"Weapon/Protector/Accessory can be acquired through the Battle, but also can be purchased from Arms Dealer. Visit Arms Dealer in Market place."
27329	"There is the size limitation for Item Storage. Therefore it is better to sell useless items and exchange to Gold Coins. Try to sell one of useless items in the Storage."
27331	"Hero should need a splendid weapon which is suitable for the Hero. Visit the Arm Dealer in Market place and purchase a weapon."
27332	"Savage tribe is attacking. Let them taste the bitterness and need to make sure them to know #nick# is the lord of this area. Exterminate all of teh Savage marauders."
27333	"Visit the barrack and encourage the generals."
27334	"Kill the Ssavage tribe"
27335	"Savage tribe chieftain is after Laboratory. Destroy the Savage tribe chieftain"
27336	"Maximum number of troops has been increased because of lord's level up. Transfer one of Heros to the Corps"
27337	"Someone wants to see the lord. Meet the person"
27338	"Secured the Laboratory. Visit the Laboratory."
27339	"Found the castle who is hostile to us. Defeat them."
27341	"All preparation is completed. This is the time to spread the lord's name to all of continents. Conquer the enemy monarch's castle"
39049	"Main Road"
39050	"Access Road"
45111	"This is the key for opening the gate to access to the next zone."
55016	"How about stopping by the weapon shop and change the weapon?"
55515	"Try to visit the weapon shop occasionally. It says that they are getting powerful new items everyday."
60517	"#duration#per second attack power #ability# is increasing."
60618	"Bleeding arrow"
60621	"It gives damage to the #ability# and at the same time it takes sight from opponent so that decreases the accuracy rate of #ability2#."
70000	"Lrd, #nick#! Are you safe!"
70001	"It looks like we managed to ditch the tail of Empire troops."
70002	"But most of them has been annihilated and remained generals are only three."
70003	"It looks like an old ruined castle."
70004	"It seems to be shabby but it will not be problem to stay if we fix it little bit."
70005	"Please, establish the foothold to build unified kingdom after regain the power and finish the Empire's tyranny."
70006	"First, there is hostile Savage tribe surround us. We need to exterminate them and bring the security to this area"
70007	"And all required operations, which has to be done, are recorded in here so that lord can see them at any time. Now see the first operation."
70008	"This is the mission lord has to do."
70009	"When you accomplish the mission you will get reward."
70010	"If you don'y know the mission location then press this."
70011	"This is mission targte.  Do not touch it."
70012	"Now start the scouting"
70013	"This is the formation of the enemy troops."
70014	"Now exit again"
70015	"When the mission is accomplished then it indicates like this."
70016	"When you press it then the mission is over with reward."
70017	"Received new mission. Press it"
70018	"Need many capable Generals(Heros) to lead many soldiers in the battle."
70019	"Now let's see the lord's Generals before the battle"
70020	"This place is for the managing and training of Generals."
70021	"Need many capable Generals(Heros) to lead many soldiers in the battle."
70022	"This place is the list of Generals lord have currently."
70023	"Every Hero has three arm of service types."
70024	"There are Defense type, Long range type, Speed type."
70025	"It is me. Press it"
70026	"It is me"
70030	"This is current level of Hero. Through the Battle, it will increase."
70031	"This is ability level of Hero. Hero will amplify the ability of the Hero's troops."
70032	"Therefore power of soldiers with better Generals gets stronger."
70036	"This is the Soldiers(Unit) Hero currently leads."
70037	"I am Long range type so I am leading Arcane Archers who are of course Long range type,"
70038	"Defense type Heros only can lead the Defense Unit such as Holly Spearman, Minotaur, Golem and so on."
70039	"It is same for the Speed type Hero"
70040	"Now let's return to the Main"
70041	"Now it is time to destroy our enemy. Touch the enemy's spot."
70042	"You can change the Troops formation before getting into the Battle."
70043	"It is better to have advantageous formation compare to enemy's formation"
70044	"First row is Defense Unit as Shield. In other words, it is better to have a formation with Spearman Unit."
70045	"They are armed with a lot of stamina and remarkable defensive power so that they are good for defending the enemy's attack."
70046	"However, their speed is very slow so it is better to put them on the first row."
70047	"This is my Troop."
70048	"I am an Archer troop who hits enemy from long range so that it is better for me to go to rear row."
70049	"Long range troop has excellent attack power and they can kill enemys from rear row."
70050	"But if their close-troop gets attack then they cannot shoot the arrows and they will be useless."
70051	"Therefore we need to protect them from approaching of enemy's close-troop."
70052	"Move my troop to the back. You can touch and then push my troop."
70053	"You did good."
70054	"Now start the attack"
70056	"Secured the Laboratory. Go to the Laboratory"
70057	"The Laboratory is the agency place where can develop our soldiers' combat ability."
70058	"First, choose a soldier you want to study. Try to develop Arcane archer's ability."
70059	"We need this resource for research."
70060	"We need this time for research."
70061	"Now you have to choose a unit character you want to develop. Press + button after you choose a skill you want"
70062	"Good. And after research time is over, soldier will be much stronger."
70063	"There are two ways to increase the Hero's level."
70064	"The first way to increase level is receiving experience points by participating the Battle"
70065	"The second way to increase the experience points is proving a experience point book which you got as a trophy to Hero without participating the Battle."
70066	"You can give expierence points by providing a book to Hero at this place."
70067	"The list of lord's possessed books is shown at this place. The book must be clan's book which Hero belongs to"
70068	"Now choose the book."
70069	"When you choose the book you want to provide, you will be get  into this slot. You can give five at once."
70070	"If you press this, the book will be provided and experience point also will be increeased."
70071	"Found Catholic church. They could give us help. For now, go to the Laboratory"
70072	"By securing Catholic church, you can secure the castle knights called <Blaze Knitage>."
70073	"Good."
70074	"They are Speed type unit so that they can penetrate enemy's rear area and neutralize the Archer troop or,"
70075	"They are close-damage dealer who makes the defense type troop like Spearman troop go ahead and then give huge damage to the enemy at the side area."
70076	"But for the disadvantage, they are weak of stamina and defense power so that if they have direct combat with enemy's defense troop they will have huge damage."
70077	"You must need Speed type Knight Hero to lead this Knightage."
70078	"Unfortnately we cannot use until we recruit the Knight Hero becasue we do not have a Knight Hero at our camp"
70079	"Welcome~ I am the Trader who goes all around the world and trades rare resources"
70080	"I will buy resources and give you Gold coins."
70081	"Lumber/Steel is little cheap, Mandrake is the most expensive. As you see, high quality resources will get higher price."
70082	"I will give you better price so let's have more business in future he he"
70083	"So....about resource price......"
70084	"How amny times you have checked before you come here?"
70085	"-_-;;;;(깊은빡침)"
70092	"You need to transfer you new received General to Corps.  Go to the Barracks."
70093	"Drag the Knight and move to Legion slot"
70094	"Good job. Now you can operate <Blaze Knightage> so enemy's Archer troop  will be dead"
70095	"This is the place where Heros from every place can have beer and chicken while they are staying."
70096	"Please, visit here more often since lord needs more elite persons (like me..) for lord's great work"
70097	"So let's try to find someone who is useful. Go to the lodging."
70098	"Need some expense payment to recruit the Hero."
70099	"If you give some gold coin in his hand then he will come with us gladly."
70100	"But if you want to hire excellent  Hero then the payment will be more expensive"
70102	"Generally you can get either Normal class Hero (1star) or Veteran class Hero(2star), but if you are lucky then you could find Rare class Hero(3star)."
70103	"Of course, if you make more expensive payment then you can hire Rare class Hero(3star) immediately, and sometimes you could find better than Epic class Hero(4star) with luck."
70107	"Go to the Barracks"
70108	"Choose me"
70112	"Lord's own power is not enough to complete the great task of continent unity."
70113	"There are many monarchs from different castles who has same vision as lord. Find them and make federation to stand against the Empire."
70114	"You have found the Embassy so now you can make federation."
70115	"Go to the Embassy"
70117	"What are you saying? You think you saw me at the Market place? I don't think so. It is first time for me..."
70118	"If you think you saw me at the Market place then maybe becasue......"
70119	"It is maybe because of your feeling."
70120	"Then I will briefly introduce about federation"
70121	"Federation is a organization where you can make alliance with friends and fight against other powers."
70122	"Of course friends cannot attack each other"
70123	"We also have Raid mission which is about defeating powerful Empire bosses with friends"
70124	"Besides, friends can help during the battle. "
70125	"Isn't it indispensable organization?"
70126	"You can make a federation by yourself so that other friends can join"
70127	"Or you can join the other federation already existed. Well, you can do whatever you want."
70128	"Now you know roughly, try to find friends."
70133	"While battle size is getting bigger, number of soldiers are insufficient."
70134	"No matter how good the Hero, if soldiers who follow hero are insufficient then they cannot fight properly."
70147	"Report!"
70148	"While we were scouting we found other monarch's castle!"
70149	"This monarch is also fighting against Empire but in order to have the power for this region, he is not goint to let us, who is located right beside of him, go."
70150	"It is difficult to keep leave it because it is big threatening element to us."
70151	"Still our army force is little weak so when the force gets stronger it is better to launch preemptive attack without any hesitation."
70152	"If you scout the enemy, you can learn their combat power. You will know by the name of the color at once"
70153	"Color grade is shown comparison with lord's combat power,"
70154	"Yellow color means combat power is alike with us. It is worth to fight."
70155	"Green color means combat power is lower so that we can easily win."
70156	"There is also gray color and it means combat power is very low so that it is not worth to fight."
70157	"While orange color means very strong opponent.  It is worth to challenge but it will not be easy to deal with."
70158	"And finally the black color means combat power is much higher than us so that in fact it is impossible to win."
70159	"However there is weakness that the reward is get bigger for the opponent who is hard to deal with and reward is get smaller for the opponent who is easy to deal with"
70160	"Therefore it is good to decide to attack after confirm the opponent's combat power level through scouting before the battle."
70161	"Also, from the scouting you can learn opponent's exact combat power level and the amount of resources you can plunder."
70162	"It was difficult battle. Congratulations on your victory."
70163	"Now our existence is known to the outsid so that attacks from other hostile monarchs will be continued while you are absent."
70164	"But the best defense strategy is attack."
70165	"You have to consistently develop generals and expand your influence by getting rid of any threatening element around you."
70166	"Fro now on you can use training camp."
70169	"Let's try training."
70185	"Gemstone resource is needed for skill training."
70186	"Gemstone can be found on 12 level area gemstone mine but we have not explored that area therefore we have to get it by pludering Empire troops for now."
70187	"They maybe have little amount of gemstone or other resources."
70188	"Like troops training is important, necessary resources is also needed as high quality resources."
70189	"For troops training, two resources such as sulfur and Mandrake are needed."
70190	"Sulfur can be received from 15 level volcano area but we have not explored that area therefore we have to get it by pludering Empire troops for now."
80193	"Remaining time %02d:%02d:%02d"
80208	"Remaining time %02d:%02d"
80209	"You are work hard by running raid. Choose one."
90000	"Conquerors : Wind of chaos"
90004	"Character research has been completed"
90005	"Trader has been returned"
90006	"Arms Dealer item has been renewed"
90007	"Got attack from %s"

5082	"Sell the item."
5087	"Change the formation of the troop."
5088	"Perform the Hero level training."
5089	"Perform the Hero skill training."
5090	"Perform the Hero troops training."
5091	"Make or join the federation."
5092	"Install the Equipment item."
5093	"Visit barracks"
5094	"Transfer a Hero to legion"
5095	"Visit Laboratory"
5097	"Scout other player's castle"
5098	"Conquer other player's castle"
80177	"On inspecting."
80178	"Monarch who is not belong to federation."
80179	"Monarch who is belong to the other federation."
80180	"No authority"
80181	"Federation with full of members."
80182	"Federation without recruiting members."
80183	"On preparing"
80184	"Federation formatting error"
80185	"Have to delegate the federation head title  to other monarch."
80186	"Not existence federation."
80187	"Are you sure to withdraw?"
80188	"Have to delegate the federation head title  to other monarch."
80189	"Start the battle"
80191	"Combat power: %d"
80192	"Today's remaining number of challenges: %d/%d"
80201	"%s/time"
80202	"Acquirable item"
80203	"Acting power used up"
80204	"Are you withdraw %s ?"
80205	"Summon"
80206	"Promoted"
80207	"Remained number of challenges"
