
// 아이디 다음의 문자열에 공백이 들어갈 경우는 반드시 따옴표를 붙이시오
// 1~999는 시스템 예약이니 사용하지 말것.
// 1~499는 번역할것
1	"Notice"
2	"OK"
3	"Cancel"
4	"YES"
5	"NO"
6	"Trying to sever connecting. Please try later."
7	"Can't connect to sever. Check your network."
8	"Close"
9	"Download the new file. If the network is no WiFi, you may excessive fee occurs."
10	"Error. Please restart your app."

// 스크립트에서 사용하는 예약어들(500~999 번역 금지)
// 500	
// 스크립트에서 사용하는 예약어들(1000~1999 번역 금지)
1000	"창병"
1001	"궁수"
1002	"팔라딘"
1003	"미노타우르스"
1004	"사이클롭스"
1005	"라이칸"
1006	"골렘"
1007	"앤트"
1008	"타천사"
1009	"추가능력치"
1010	"추가능력치직업"
1011	"수면"
1012	"기절"
1013	"스턴"
1014	"포박"
1015	"출혈"
1016	"중독"
1017	"암흑"
1018	"둔화"
1019	"혼란"
1020	"공포"
1021	"침묵"
1022	"투명화"
1023	"휘감기"
1024	"추가능력치종족"
1025	"기사"
1026	"미노"
1027	"사이"
1028	"라이"
1029	"타천"
1030	"인간"
1031	"짐승"
1032	"몬스터"
1033	"악마"
1034	"소형"
1035	"중형"
1036	"대형"
1037	"전투시작시"
1038	"빙결"
1039	"소형공속보정"
1040	"중형공속보정"
1041	"대형공속보정"
1042	"도발"
1043	"종족"
1044	"직업"
1045	"병과"
1046	"크기"
1047	"탱커"
1048	"원거리"
1049	"스피드"
1050	"계급"
1051	"병사"
1052	"영웅"
1053	"소형피해보정"
1054	"중형피해보정"
1055	"대형피해보정"
1056	"근접형피해보정"
1057	"원거리형피해보정"
1058	"스피드형피해보정"
1059	"얼음"
1060	"창병피해보정"
1061	"궁수피해보정"
1062	"기사피해보정"
1063	"미노피해보정"
1064	"사이피해보정"
1065	"라이피해보정"
1066	"골렘피해보정"
1067	"앤트피해보정"
1068	"타천피해보정"
1069	"화상"
1070	"분노"
1071	"소형회피율보정"
1072	"중형회피율보정"
1073	"대형회피율보정"

// 시스템 예약어 끝
////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
// 이하는 유저대상 메시지들(로컬라이징 대상임)
2000	"none"
2001	"Barbarians"
2002	"You need more Item."
2003	"You want to sell it?"
2004	"You want to use it?"
2005	"You want to increase your storage?"
2006	"You can't Upgrade no more."
2007	"Wood"
2008	"Iron"
2009	"Jewel"
2010	"Sulfur"
2011	"Mandrake"
2012	"Imperial troops"
2013	"Goal"
2014	"Reward"
2015	"Mission complete"
2016	"Reward EXP:%d"
2017	"Research cost"
2018	"Research Time"
2019	"Necessary level"
2020	"Sulfur convoy"
2021	"Position"
2022	"Lock"
2023	"Unlock"
2024	"Trait point"
2025	"Valiancy point"
2026	"Necessary Valiancy point"
2027	"Complete"
2028	"Researching other Trait now."
2029	"The research of '%s' was completed."
2030	"None"
2031	"Surprise attack"
2032	"Attack"
2033	"Retreat"
2034	"We came under attack from enemy. If you lose the battle, lost your sulfur."
2035	"You didn’t have reconnaissance."
2036	"Production: %d/h"
2037	"Total stock:%.1f"
2038	"Battle"
2039	"Ready"
2040	"Resource"
2041	"Attack Record"
2042	"Defense Record"
2043	"Replay"
2044	"Revenge"
2045	"Reward"
2046	"Number of Winning Streak"
2047	"Winning Streak"
2048	"Total reward"
2049	"%dWin"
2050	"Search Crow Clan Tokens."
2051	"Please change your book for Hero Exp through Tokens."
2052	"Search Iron Lord Clan Tokens"
2053	"Search Liberty Alliance Clan Tokens"
2054	"Search Ancient civilizations Clan Tokens"
2055	"Search Flame Clan Tokens "
2056	"Price:"
2057	"Installation Effect"
2060	"Sword"
2061	"Axe"
2062	"Dagger"
2063	"Blunt weapon"
2064	"Staff"
2065	"Wand"
2066	"Spear"
2067	"Weapon"
2068	"Armor"
2069	"Helmet"
2070	"Glove"
2071	"Shoes"
2072	"Accessories"
2073	"Nomal"
2074	"Luxury"
2075	"Rare"
2076	"Hero"
2077	"Legend"
2078	"Finish now"
2079	"Total Dealing"
2080	"Total Damage"
2081	"Total Critical Damage"
2082	"Total evasion"
2083	"Total healing"
2084	"Total Regeneration"
2085	"Total skill damage"
2086	"Statistics"
2087	"%s Hero is in use. Please lift installation. "
2088	"Necessary %d hero's level"
2089	"Not enough level."
2090	"Start Training"
2091	"Necessary resource"
2092	"Hero %s was up to %d level!"
2093	"There is no empty training camp."
2094	"Hero %s troop was up to %d level!"
2095	"Hero %s skill %s was up to %d level!"
2096	"영웅 %s의 훈련이 끝났습니다."
2097	"Barrack"
2098	"군주님의 레벨이 %d{이/가} 되었습니다!"
2099	"Max AP"
2100	"새 특성 포인트 획득!"
2101	"Maximum troops"
2102	"%, %s, %s can be used."
2103	"Active skill"
2104	"Leader skill"
2105	"Not on research"
2106	"Unknown error"
2107	"Log in"
2108	"Soldier of information"
2109	"You have to unlocking the soldier's lock."
2110	"User level %d필요"
2111	"Max Level"
2112	"AP"
2113	"상대 플레이어가 온라인 상태여서 공격할 수 없습니다."
2114	"공격받고 있습니다. 잠시 기다려 주십시오."
2115	"Power"
2116	"Do you have already account?"
2117	"군주님이 자리를 비우신동안 적의 침공이 있었습니다!. 방어기록을 확인해주십시오!"
2118	"ago"
2119	"금화가 부족합니다. 캐쉬로 대신 하시겠습니까?"
2120	"자원이 부족합니다. 캐쉬로 대신 하시겠습니까?"
2121	"free"
2122	"누군가 전투중입니다."
2123	"길드레이드를 하려면 길드에 가입되어 있어야 합니다."
2124	"전투중"
2125	"공격을 시작하십시오."
2126	"Start raid"
2127	"사망"
2128	"도전은 한번만 가능합니다."
2129	"이제 [%s] 기능을 사용할 수 있게 되었습니다."
2130	"연구소"
2131	"성당"
2132	"영웅의 숙소"
2133	"군사학교"
2134	"병영"
2135	"대사관"
2140	"%s{을/를} 발견했습니다"
2141	"이제 [%s] 유닛을 사용할 수 있게되었습니다."
2142	"%s 지역을 먼저 열어야 합니다."
2143	"Not enough gold"
2144	"새로운 종류의 병사를 사용할 수 있게 되었습니다."
2145	"%s{이/가} 필요합니다."
2146	"정예"
2147	"군단"
2148	"White crow clan"
2149	"Neo-Ironlord clan"
2150	"자유동맹 탈주자"
2151	"Acient rebels"
2152	"West flame"
2153	"defense"
2154	"등장유닛"
2155	"오늘의 도전횟수를 모두 사용했습니다."
2156	"더이상 도전할 수 없습니다."
2157	"잠겨 있습니다."
2158	"%s's soul stone"
2159	"영혼석을 모아 %s 영웅을 승급시키거나 소환시킵니다."
2160	"레벨%d 필요"
2200	"Not enough action point(AP:%d)"
2201	"need AP"
2202	"All fill"
2203	"Provide one"
2204	"Drag your hero, place the slot"

//        x
4999	""
5000	"Crow"
5001	"Iron Lord"
5002	"Liberty Alliance"
5003	"Ancient civilization"
5004	"Flame"
5005	"Please get #what# level."
5006	"#what# area open."
5007	"Kill #what#."
5008	"Reconnoiter #what#."
5009	"Visit #what#."
5010	"Kill #what#."
5011	"Attack #what#."
5012	"Recon #what#."
5013	"Visit #what#."
5014	"Please get #what# hero."
5015	"Kill #what#."
5016	"Complete #what# mission."
5017	"Defend your Catsle."
5018	"Please get #what#."
5019	"Have #what#."
5020	"Please get #what#."
5021	"Have #what#."
5022	"Conquer #what#."
5023	""
5039	""
5040	"from #where#"
5041	"Kill #where#"
5042	"from #where#"
5043	""
5070	"Other lord's Castle"
5071	"Jewel mine"
5072	"Sulphur carriage"
5073	"Mandrake Farm"
5074	"Enemy"
5075	"Operation area"
5076	"Visit area"
5080	""


//        유저대상 메시지들 끝.
//     영웅 이름
10000	"skar"
10001	"zanta"
10002	"unluny"
10003	"frio"
10004	"fei"
10005	"enloque"
10006	"bruxa"
10007	"sinceridade"
10008	"thompson "
10009	"al"
10010	"ed"
10011	"michael "
10012	"spawn "
10013	"kane "
10014	"peter "
10015	"porter "
10016	"molly"
10017	"gamelan "
10018	"ahramodeu "
10019	"pell "
10020	"teen "
10021	"ton "
10022	"kashi "
10023	"scar "
10024	"ador "
10025	"meltin "
10026	"ivan "
10027	"knife "
10028	"raul "
10029	"ron "
10030	"ogma "
10031	"chris "
10032	"unlike "
10033	"jyulra "
10034	"ricky "
10035	"rai "
10036	"roy "
10037	"louis "
10038	"ray "
10039	"molloy "
10040	"malvine "
10041	"mason "
10042	"mike "
10043	"brandon "
10044	"barton "
10045	"rice "
10046	"baker "
10047	"brans "
10048	"broms"
10049	"becky "
10050	"rom "
10051	"rudy "
10052	"roll "
10053	"lal "
10054	"james "
10055	"jason "
10056	"jude "
10057	"jerry "
10058	"jed"
10059	"joy "
10060	"zone "
10061	"tom"
10062	"alleg"
10063	"king minotawooreuseu"
10064	"boss balor"
10065	"rycan prince"
10066	"ollen"
10067	"dixon"
10068	"jade"
10069	"demigun"
10070	"linus"
10071	"philoni"
10072	"yidel"
10073	"arlene"
10074	"dorian"
10075	"irina"
10076	"sarina"
10077	"nay"
10078	"marie"
10079	"moriya"
10080	"speedy"
10081	"carlya"
10082	"rossnam"
10083	"rotapio"
10084	"colliemeg"
10085	"progun"
10086	"asupa"
10087	"dyamu"
10088	"adiple"
10089	"giltyuer"
10090	"gilbert"
10091	"nolehmann"
10092	"seri"
10093	"syrina"
10094	"megan"
10095	"mina"
10096	"julia"
10097	"kara"
10098	"helena"
10099	"marina"
10100	"irelna"
10101	"nadia"
10102	"collie"
10103	"asia"
10104	"tia"
10105	"noah"
10106	"easy"
10107	"jinullee"
10108	"homeli"
10109	"hefrio"
10110	"lanoro"
10111	"prenoth"
10112	"hetribs"
10113	"congent"
10114	"laynar"
10115	"donkey xote"


// 퀘스트 관련
15000	""
15001	"Medius valley"
15002	""
15003	""
15004	"Evil Monster"
15005	"Elite Imperials"
15006	"Storm banditry"
15007	"Last Storm banditry"
15008	"Bomber"
15009	"Fallen Imperials"
15010	"Witch's house"
15011	"Forest of Ancient Ent"
15012	"Imperials"
15013	"New blacksmith"
15014	"Minotaur Hell's Labyrinth"
15015	"Cyclope rock mountain"
15016	"Eksillease sulfur zone"
15017	"Brotherhood of Fire"
15018	"Carpenter"
15019	"Information analtst"
15020	"Brotherhood of Fire's secret base"
15021	"Fire Priest Malbadu"
15022	"Location of relic"
15023	"Info of Barbarian"
15024	"bellado forest's maze cave"
15025	"Flame Clan"
15026	"Magma Golem area"
15027	"Liberty Alliance Clan"
15028	"Imperials have acquired Freedom Watch"
15029	"Fallen Angel's boss Idraell"
15030	"Crow Clan"
15031	"Strategic point of Imperials"
15032	"Imperials strategic point"
15033	"Iron Lord Clan"
15034	"Laboratory of Imperials"
15035	"Messengers of Ancient civilizations Clan"
15036	"Hidden last relic"
15037	"Scout"
15038	"Deep in the forest cave"
15039	"Info of the Barbarian"
15040	"Mercenary troops shelter"
15041	"Blacksmith smith"
15042	"Closed Mine"
15043	"Evil Monster Cave"
15044	"Bandits"
15045	"고대문명 클랜"
15046	"콘티구스 용암동굴"
15047	"정체불명의 부대"
15048	"범인의 용병부대"
15049	"마물 부대"
15050	"황제군의 정보"
15051	"이드마크의 마물부대"
15052	"노예시장 용병"
15053	"벨라도 산적"
15054	"검날이 봉인된 동굴"
15055	"기아모프의 별장"
15056	"성"
15057	"얄루 야만족"
15058	"붉은 강철 약탈부대"
15059	"무법자"
15060	"타락 창병부대"
15061	"난폭해진 엔트의 숲"
15062	"오드로프의 정찰부대"
15063	"오드로프 호위부대"
15064	"현자의 집"

// 퀘스트 
20000	"#what# area open"
20001	"#what# area open"
20002	"#spot# Battle"
20003	"#num#win #spot#."
20004	"#item# collection "
20005	"Collect #num# #item#."
20006	"Kill #hero# of #area#."
20007	"This old froest has been preserved since ancient times. "
20008	"This old froest has been preserved since ancient times. But Imperials is destroying here. Please stop them."
20009	"Hello. Lord. I'm smith and new blacksmith."
20010	"Reconstruction"
20011	"We have to find power. Please upgrade level."
20012	"Achieve #what# level"
20013	""
20014	"Extend power"
20015	"You has little power. you have to go wide area. Please go Medius valley."
20016	"Medius valley exploration"
20017	"Attack the Imperial's scout"
20018	"The Imperial's scout is in this area. If you don't atattack them, our troops are discovered by enemy.  "
20019	"Attack the Imperial's scout"
20020	"Meet the master"
20021	"Meet 5 Clan master"
20022	"Meet the Crow Clan Master"
20023	"Meet the Liberty Alliance Clan Master "
20024	"Meet the Iron Lord Clan Master "
20025	"Meet the Ancient civilizations Clan Master "
20026	"Meet the Flame Clan Master"
20027	"Imperial's scout"
20028	"Crow Clan's hideout"
20029	"Liberty Alliance Clan's hideout"
20030	"Iron Lord Clan's hideout"
20031	"Ancient civilizations Clan's hide out"
20032	"Flame Clan's hideout"
20033	"I'm Master Crow of Crow Clan. Our clan's demand is all clan's 1 token. We like all kinds of token.  "
20034	"I'm Zanta of Liberty Alliance. If you attack Bandits around castle area , I will offer a big reward. "
20035	"I'm Bellbyar of Iron lord. If you suppress lords, I will offer a big reward. "
20036	"I'm Mtstica of Ancient civilizations Clan. We need our token."
20037	"I'm adorue and Boss of Flame clan. Our request is Barbarian's Falen shard."
20038	"Kill banditry"
20039	"Please kill banditry."
20040	"Kill banditry"
20041	"Meet the fire Priest"
20042	"The Priest of Red robe want to meet #Player#. Please meet him."
20043	"Visitor"
20044	"One thousand years ago, we sealed the evil ancient wizard with 5 noble family and Brotherhood of Fire.But strange incident is happening in some continent. Would you examine about sanctum? If you help me, I will offer reward."
20045	"Medius Lake Exploation"
20046	"Sanctum of Lake"
20047	"The Sanctum was destroyed by Imperial's troops. They stole the halidom. Please kill them."
20048	"#what# Kill"
20049	"Please kill #what# at the #where#."
20050	"I requested this item. I will make sword by this item. Please wait."
20051	"Crow Clan Request"
20052	"Kill emeies and gather 5 noble family's tokens from them."
20053	"Liberty Alliance Request"
20054	"Kill Bandits"
20055	"Iron Lord Clan Request"
20056	"Please Occupy castle."
20057	"Ancient civilizations Clan Request"
20058	"Ancient civilizations Clan's Tokens Collection "
20059	"Flame Clan의 Request"
20060	"Barbarian's Fallen shard Recovery"
20061	"How did you feel when you collected the Tokens from 5 Clans? That was fun? But you have to be careful. Clan's heroes very strong. I wanna give you a hero. Thank you."
20062	"The bandits disappeard. Many people will live more comfortably. I support the hero of Liberty Alliance. Thank you."
20063	"Many lord will plunder our resource. You have to be careful. I send you our clan's hero."
20064	"Thank you. You can deal with Ancient civilizations Clan. See you later after using our hero."
20065	"Thank you. This Fallen shard have become more vicious! Let's fight with our clan's hero! Haha."
20066	"Ring of Evil Monster..Because of the Evil Monster and wizard's contract, the ring has Evil Monster control power.Unfortunately, that ring is not producing but old wizard's ring is still in existence.But Evil Monster is hiding that. But I know information of ring. You want to hear? Oh, I'm short of jewel..It's a headache. "
20067	"Oh.. We are over the worst. I tell you my information. Minotaur of Barbarians recorded Labyrinth area.But the Barbarians was killed by Minotaur Hell and their map was scattered. The Babarians are storing map piece. Helpful?"
20068	"Ring of Evil Monster"
20069	"Meet the trader"
20070	"Information Reward"
20071	"Collect jewel"
20072	"Contract with Minotaur Hell"
20073	"Meet the trader"
20074	"Minotaur Hell Labyrinth"
20075	"Collect map piece of Minotaur Hell's Labyrinth"
20076	"Labyrinth Entry"
20077	"Minotaur Hell Labyrinth Clear"
20078	"Cyclope's ring"
20079	"Meet the trader"
20080	"Rock mountain of Cyclope"
20081	"Collect  Iron ore"
20082	"Rock mountain Entry"
20083	"Rock mountain of Cyclope Clear"
20084	"Big Lycan's ring"
20085	"Meet the trader"
20086	"Secret area of Big Lycan"
20087	"Get map of Big Lycan secret area"
20088	"Secret area Entry"
20089	"Secret area of Big Lycan Clear"
20090	"Battle with Alleg"
20091	"Kill Alleg"
20092	"Go Eksillease sulfur zone"
20093	"Open Eksillease sulfur zone"
20094	"Obstacle"
20095	"Attack the eksillease sulfur zone's Castle"
20096	"Suspicious movement"
20097	"Visit Brotherhood of Fire "
20098	"Fire Soldiers"
20099	"Fire Soldiers Clear"
20100	"I got the information about the contracted ring. The Cyclope is guarding the ring. But If you want more information, you have to pay for something."
20101	"The ring is in the rock mountain of astrellranch. You have to be careful that Cyclope is very wild."
20102	"Contracted Big Lycan's ring...I know some information but that is not sure.But I tell you because you wanna this. I heard that unknown Mercenaries unit came Big Lycan's secret area.They could have made map. Could you check this uncertain information?"
20103	"Information Reward"
20104	"Meet the trader"
20105	"interrupt consciousness!"
20106	"You gatherd all piece of map. Let's find mystrey area using map piece. According to the map that area is jewel mine of astrellranch."
20107	"Finished map"
20108	"I'll tell about Big Lycan information. The Big Lycan's secret area is arround medius valley. In that area the Big Lycan is protecting contracted ring. helpful?"
20109	"If you repair the castle, you need many wood and Iron. Please gather that and bring me."
20110	"Oh, you gathered all. I'll repair the castle now."
20111	"Castle repqir"
20112	"Meet the Carpenter"
20113	"Collect of repair material castle "
20114	"Collect wood and Iron"
20115	"Material Delivery"
20116	"After a battle with the barbarians lifted their horses that they're going to try to do something in the Deep in belladoHoly Land. Find relics must be returned to them before it is too late."
20117	"For the vellado"
20118	"Secure bellado's access road "
20119	"Brotherhood of Fire's mark"
20120	"Barbarians with Battle"
20121	"Brotherhood of Fire to area"
20122	"Talking with information analyst"
20123	"Secure bellado Holy Land "
20124	"Secure bellado Holy Land "
20125	"Brotherhood of Fire's secret base"
20126	"Clear the Brotherhood of Fire's secret base"
20127	"Brotherhood of Fire"
20128	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20129	"sulfur zone's relic"
20130	"Clear sulfur zone's relic"
20131	"Second information of relic"
20132	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu"
20133	"Hidden relic"
20134	"Battle with Barbarians"
20135	"Information of Barbarians"
20136	"Listen Information of Barbarians  "
20137	"Secret Cave"
20138	"Clear Secret Cave"
20139	"Third relic"
20140	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20141	"Secret Mine"
20142	"Clear Secret Mine"
20143	"Relic Seal"
20144	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20145	"Deal with Flame Clan"
20146	"Talking with Flame Clan's Master"
20147	"Flame Clan's condition"
20148	"Clear Magma Golem area in eksillease "
20149	"Flame Unseal"
20150	"Talking with Flame Clan's Master"
20151	"Fourth relic"
20152	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20153	"Forest of ent"
20154	"Clear Forest of ent in Kopiosus field "
20155	"Liberty Alliance Seal"
20156	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20157	"Promise with Liberty Alliance"
20158	"Talking with Liberty Alliance's Master"
20159	"Trader's Information"
20160	"Talking with trader"
20161	"Freedom Watch area"
20162	"Get Freedom Watch"
20163	"Freedom Unseal"
20164	"Talking with Liberty Alliance's Master"
20165	"Fifth relic"
20166	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20167	"Fallen Angel's nest"
20168	"Clear Fallen Angel's nest"
20169	"Fallen Angel's ring"
20170	"Talking with Fallen Angel's Master"
20171	"Recapture God's Sanctuary"
20172	"Clear God's Sanctuary"
20173	"Fallen Angel's ring"
20174	"Talking with Fallen Angel's Master"
20175	"Seal ]of Crow "
20176	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20177	"Crow's remand"
20178	"Talking with Crow Clan's Master"
20179	"Imperials Strategic point"
20180	"Clear Imperials Strategic point"
20181	"Crow unseal"
20182	"Talking with Crow Clan's Master"
20183	"Sixth relic"
20184	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20185	"Imperials's Military area"
20186	"Clear the Imperials's Military area"
20187	"Iron Lord seal"
20188	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20189	"Iron Lord Clan's condition"
20190	"Talking with Iron Lord Clan's Master"
20191	"Iron Compass's whereabouts"
20192	"Battle with Barbarians"
20193	"Mandrake field's compass"
20194	"Listen Information of Barbarians  "
20195	"Iron Compass"
20196	"Clear the Imperials's Iron watch"
20197	"Iron Lord unseal"
20198	"Talking with Iron Lord Clan's Master"
20199	"Seventh relic"
20200	"Talking with Fire Priest Malbadu in castle"
20201	"Ancient civilizations Clan's warning"
20202	"Talking with Ancient civilizations's lion in castle"
20203	"Secret cave of konjutou's hole "
20204	"Clear Secret cave of konjutou's hole "
20205	"Getaway"
20206	"Talking with soldier in castle"
20207	"The rituals of fire "
20208	"Event"
20209	"I'm Fire Priest Malbadu. Imperials is  trying to gather Wizard Merlin's relic. we are threatened by them, because we knows relic's whereabouts. The relic isn't never fall into their hands. I need your help. Please collect relic in contigus."
20210	"The relic is hidden secret code for next relic. So we know next relic in bellado forest, but that is uncertain. Firstly, we have to find relic's whereabouts."
20211	"I don't know relic..But I have been saw secret cave, I feel relic is there.. Isn't it?"
20212	"This is second relic. Maybe next relic is in the Praepujench mine. The record is exact and your are not difficultly finding relic."
20213	"Um..Just aquire relic was unsealed..The seal's trace is Flame Clan's way. If you want to unseal this, you have to talking with Flame Clan's Master"
20214	"Hmm..Seal.. I can unseal this, but I have demand condition. That condition is to remove Magma Golem!If you remove Magma Golem in eksilleas, I'll unseal that."
20215	"Good. I will comply with requirement. I unseal this now. And thank your eradication. "
20216	"Oh..Finally the seal is unseal.. The next relic is in Kopiosus field. This root code suggest ent's region."
20217	"This reilc sealed too. This way is Alliance's seal. You have to talk with Liberty Alliance this time."
20218	"You want to seal this relic? This is ours, but we need freedom watch for seal this. But 30 years ago, that was stolen. If you find freedom watch, I can seal that."
20219	"Freedom watch.. Oh I remember that. The watch is used in readout secret document and that was produced 1000 years ago, remain a watch. But the watch was stolen..That's too bad. I have information about Freedom watch. Imperials gathered at the lebuus mountain for finding freedom watch. "
20220	"Really thank you..I can't find this stolen watch. I will seal by this thing."
20221	"Oh, You can seal secret cord. The next relic is maybe in Knjutou. But there residence is Fallen Angel now.Not easy this time…"
20222	"Did you hurt our fallen angels because this relic? I can't give it to you. If you want to this, you have to count the cost. God's Sanctuary is arround near here. We need the energy of God's Sanctuary. If you kill them and give us God's Sanctuary, I'll give you relic."
20223	"Oh, you are so awesome. Good. I'll give you the contractual ring with us. I can get the God's sanctuary, thanks to your help. I'll play with you."
20224	"This is fifth relic. I'm very excited about it. Let's find sixth relic's location. This relic was unsealed too.This is Crow Clan's seal. You can do it."
20225	"Long time no see. Do you want to unseal this? This is not easy! Do I look too easy to get the short end of it?If you want to unseal, attack the Imperials's center. I was commissioned to kill them. But that is difficult for me. I'll unseal this. Thank you~ "
20226	"Wow~ Thank you! That request was difficult for me. I'll give you a reward. I unsealed this! Let's try to get along from now on."
20227	"There is just a little more. The sixth reilc is in laksuss. I remebered that is in Imperials's strategic point.The relic reads us to scary place….."
20228	"We only have a bit more to go till we reach our goal. This sixth relic sealed state.. This is Iron Lord."
20229	"That relic is ours. This is relic of Iron Compass. But I can't seal this because Iron Compass disappeared 30 years ago. I suspect some place..But I can't go there because relationship with Imperials. If you help us, I can seal this relic. I suspected the forest of amplro river. Please find Iron Compass in forest of amplro river.
"
20230	"Imperials took the Iron compass five years ago. Rumor has it that they took the Iron compass for Imperials's laboratory three years ago. Why don't you go there? "
20231	"Thank you. I become more confident to ancestors. This relic was unsealed. The ancestors has to be a reason for their seal. Be careful."
20232	"You can find last relic's location. The last relic is in konjutou hall. The two relic exist there. Please find relic in konjutou hall. "
20233	"You shouldn't find last relic. And there's a reason for that. Be careful."
20234	"That's terrible. Fire Priest was felling with relic for konjutou hall."
20235	"holy Spearman Reinforcements"
20236	"Let's collect Hand to hand combat Medal for holy Spearman Reinforcements."
20237	"Arcane snifer Reinforcements"
20238	"Let's collect Hand to hand combat Medal for Arcane snifer Reinforcements"
20239	"Flame Knight Reinforcements"
20240	"Let's collect Hand to hand combat Medal for Flame Knight Reinforcements"
20241	"Visit Crow Clan"
20242	"Let's visit to Crow Clan for checking equest."
20243	"In the deep woods enemy"
20244	"Let's remove crow clan's goal in medius mountain."
20245	"Request completed"
20246	"Let's visit Crow Clan and complete their request."
20247	"Visit Liberty Alliance Clan "
20248	"Let's visit to Liberty Alliance Clan for checking request of freedom alliance."
20249	"Medius Patrol"
20250	"Let's remove Medius mountain's barbarians and Imperial troops."
20251	"Request completed"
20252	"Let's visit Liberty Alliance and complete their request."
20253	"Visit Iron Lord Clan "
20254	"Let's visit to Iron Lord for checking request "
20255	"Collect Iron"
20256	"Let's collect Iron."
20257	"Request completed"
20258	"Let's visit Iron Lord and complete their request."
20259	"Mercenaries unit's rumor"
20260	"Medius mountain resident are suffering from Mercenaries unit.Let's remove Medius mountain's barbarians and Imperial troops. "
20261	"Mercenaries unit's base camp"
20262	"Let's visit to Barbarian's base."
20263	"The wandering mercenaries unit"
20264	"Let's kill the wandering mercenaries unit for resident."
20265	"Imperial's Surprise attack"
20266	"They send troops from Imperial, they were discovered. Check their troops."
20267	"Counterattack"
20268	"Checked Surprise troops, Let's counter attack!"
20269	"Find smith"
20270	"Find smith for making Hero's equipment Item."
20271	"Collect resource"
20272	"If you make Item, you need wood and Iron. Collect wood and Iron, bring to him."
20273	"Smith's Item"
20274	"You relayed the resource. Let's receive equipment."
20275	"Saving Resource"
20276	"Let's kill lord for your stolen resource."
20277	"Collect Bead in short time"
20278	"Let's attack Castle and collect Bead in short time."
20279	"Weapon resource"
20280	"Let's collect Iron, supplement for soldier's weapon."
20281	"Collect weapon"
20282	"Let's collect weapon through battle"
20283	"Headache pill"
20284	"Let's acquire headache pill through battle with emeny."
20285	"undermine morale of enemies"
20286	"Let's under mine morale through battle."
20287	"Searching structure"
20288	"The lebuus river was found doubtful structure. Let's explore here."
20289	"Rampart Upgrade"
20290	"Let's collect Iron and wood for Upgrade of Rampart."
20291	"Collect Jewel"
20292	"Let's collect Jewel"
20293	"Bandits troops"
20294	"Let's search Bandits for checking their troops. Bandits is in the astrellranch's boundary area."
20295	"Remove Bandits"
20296	"Let's remove Bandits."
20297	"collect beed in shor time 2"
20298	"Let's collect beed in shor time."
20299	"Visit Flame Clan "
20300	"Let's visit Flame Clan for exchange"
20301	"Evil Monster and human"
20302	"Let's attack the human's cave"
20303	"Report to Flame Clan"
20304	"Report to Flame Clan the Evil Monster utilizer."
20305	"Remove Barbarians and Imperial troops."
20306	"Let's remove Barbarians and Imperial troops and raise the morale."
20307	"The stolen armor"
20308	"Smith want to tell you. Let's go to him."
20309	"Armor collect"
20310	"Let's remove enemies of Medius mountain for finding armor."
20311	"Return armor to smith"
20312	"Let's return armor to smith"
20313	"castellan checks "
20314	"Let's attack castle for castellan checks."
20315	"Occupy Jewel Mine"
20316	"Let's occupy jewel mine and acquire jewel."
20317	"Clear Minotaur Hell's Labyrinth"
20318	"Let's one more clear Minotaur Hell's Labyrinth."
20319	"In Medius mountain, They love to have what they want at anyone's expense for their own gratification.Please kill them."
20320	"You successed. You made things easier for me. Client must be happy to hear that."
20321	"Hello. Our request is that you kill the barbarians and Imperial troops in Medius region.Many people suffers from them then you have to kill them."
20322	"Thank you for your effort. They will stop bullying them."
20323	"Iron Lord's request is collecting Iron. We are not enough Iron for making steel of Iron Lord symbol. So our production is delayed due to Iron.If you solve this problem, you have to request lords like you. Please."
20324	"Thank you. Our Iron Production is good. If you get this Iron, you can attack other castle or collecting.But best way is attack! I hope this information is useful to you."
20325	"I know that mercenary and I tell you their location. Please go to there."
20326	"If you make equipment, you need wood and Iron. You have too gather this thing then I'll produce that."
20327	"I can make equipment. Please wait me. This equipment is armor. Please use usefully."
20328	"Welcome! Nowdays some people are plundering by Evil Monsters! Please remove them! They are hidden in main mine of astrellranch. Please!"
20329	"How to use Evil Monster without ring of contract…I'll examine that. I think that your Evil Monster ring is not threatening. I believe you."
20330	"I have old armor in my house. Our Blacksmith family like to make their armor. Your armor made by this. But We were stolen that armor few days ago. Please find our family's armor. "
20331	"Thank you! This is my payment. Please use this."
20332	"Hello. Our request is that you kill the barbarians and Imperial troops in Medius region. Many people suffers from them then you have to kill them."
20333	"Thank you for your effort. They will stop bullying them."
20334	"어서오세요. 이번에 저희 길드의 서고에서 지도가 하나 발견되었습니다. 이 지도는 무언가 특별한 물건을 가리키고 있었죠. 근데 저희 길드에 잠입해있던 제국군의 스파이가 이 지도를 훔쳐 달아나는 사태가 발생했습니다. 다행스럽게도 스파이는 금방 잡았지만, 잡는 과정에서 지도가 그만 여러장을 찢겨 날아가버리고 말았답니다. 이 지도의 파편을 구해다 주시는 것이 저희의 의뢰예요."
20335	"지도를 모두 모아오셨군요! 이제 저희는 이 지도를 합쳐서 이 지도가 어떤 물건을 가리키고 있는 것이지 해석하는 작업에 들어갈 거예요. 저희의 해석이 끝나는대로 다시 한번 연락드리겠습니다. 이제 당신과 저희는 한 배를 탄 사이니까요."
20336	"어서오세요. 저번의 지도에 대한 해석이 모두 끝났어요. 지도가 가리키고 있는 것은 300년전 쯤에 만들어진 유물인거 같아요. 지도에 이 유물이 있는 장소는 콘티구스의 용암지의 한 동굴 같아요. 이 곳에서 유물을 회수해주시는 것이 이번 저희의 의뢰예요. 그럼 잘 부탁드려요~"
20337	"이게 그 지도에 표시된 유물이라면 무엇가 숨겨진 비밀이 있을거예요. 이제부터 저희는 이 칼자루의 분석에 들어가겠습니다. 이 칼자루의 분석이 끝나는데로 연락드리도록 하지요."
20338	"아, 어서와. 이번에 너를 부른 이유는 다름이 아니라 저번에 숲속에 잠복해 있던 부대를 해치워 달라고 의뢰를 했던 의뢰인이 행방불명이 되었다가 몇일전 시체로 발견됐어. 우리 클랜은 어떤 의뢰라도 받기 때문에 의뢰인의 정체를 누설하거나 하는 일은 없는데 말이야. 그래서 이번 의뢰인을 죽인 녀석들을 좀 찾아달라는게 우리의 의뢰야. 이번에는 우리 길드의 위신도 걸려있는 문제라서 우리도 적극적으로 움직일거야. "
20339	"흠 그 범인은 놓쳤단 말이지. 괜찮아 그놈은 우리가 처리하면 되니까 그래도 상당히 빠른 시간안에 해결해줘서 고마워. 이제 우리는 그놈을 잡아서 어떻게 알아냈는지를 좀 알아봐야겠어. 그럼 다음에도 잘 부탁해~"
20340	"갑작스러운 마물의 대규모 공격이 감지되었다! 다만 우리 길드는 저런 대규모 공격을 막기에는 어려움이 있어 자네와 같은 병사들을 이끄는 성주들의 도움이 필요하다! 자네는 저 마물들이 일제히 공격하기 전 병력을 줄이는 역할을 해주길 바란다.  "
20341	"연금술사의 문장을 지닌 한 연금술사가 마물에게 다가가 이상한 돌을 집어넣는 겁니다. 그러더니 갑자기 조용하던 마물이 흉폭해지고, 그가 조종하는 것처럼 움직이기 시작하더라구요. 아! 이제보니 그 연금술사의 문장이 기억납니다. 이드마크라고 하는 연금술사예요!"
20342	"그대 덕분에 그 수많은 마물 부대로부터 승리할 수 있었다. 하지만 이만큼의 마물 부대를 조정할 수 있었던 것이 모두 한 연금술사의 힘이라니 믿기지가 않는군. 우선 우리는 마물에게 박혀있던 분노의 핵에 대한 조사를 먼저 진행할 예정이다. 이번 그대의 노고에 감사한다."
20343	"안녕하십니까. 이번에 저희가 알아낸 정보에 따르면 몇일 후 노예시장이 열린다고 합니다. 노예제도는 이미 옛날에 사라졌지만, 아직도 노예시장을 통한 노예 거래는 비밀스럽게 진행되고 있는 것 같습니다. 이번에는 저희와 함께 이 노예시장을 찾아 그들을 처단해야합니다."
20344	"아마도 이런 노예시장이 하나만 있는 것은 아닐겁니다. 앞으로도 이와같은 싸움을 계속 하게되겠지요. 하지만 수많은 사람들의 행복과 자유를 위해서라도 저희는 움직일겁니다. 저희와 함께해주신 당신께 감사하다는 말을 드립니다. 아 그리고 이 획득하신 목걸이는 저희가 보관하겠습니다. 여기서 이 노예시장에 관여한 자가 누구인지 알아낼 수 있을지도 모르니까요."
20345	"저번에 획득한 칼자루를 분석한 결과가 나왔어요. 이 검자루에 쓰여진 글씨는 일종의 봉인의 글로 이를 해석할만한 힌트가 이 검을 획득한 곳에 남아있을거예요. 그 힌트를 알아와주세요."
20346	"아 탁본을 만들어오셨군요. 센스가 넘치시네요. 덕분에 이것으로 칼자루의 봉인을 풀고 어떤 비밀이 숨겨져있는지 알 수 있을 것 같네요. 우리는 비밀의 탐구자, 비밀의 수호자. 당신의 길에 비밀이 함께 하길"
20347	"저번의 강철을 수집하는 당신의 능력을 보고 또다른 의뢰를 하려고 한다. 이번에는 붉은 강철을 만들기 위한 재료 만드레이크를 수집해주기 바란다. 붉은 강철은 독특한 강철로 한번 녹이면 유연하지만 굳으면 매우 단단해지는 특성을 지니고 있지. 이것을 만들기 위해선 만드레이크의 피가 필요하다. 현재 다수의 성주들이 만드레이크 밭을 약탈하는 상황에서 그 성주들로부터 만드레이크를 가져오는 것이 쉽지는 않을 것이다."
20348	"흠, 질 좋은 만드레이크들이군. 이제 이것으로 우리는 붉은 강철을 만들 수 있게 되었다. 당신의 노고에 감사를 표한다."
20349	"저번의 주신 탁본을 통해서 이 검의 비밀을 알아낼 수가 있었어요. 이 검은 검자루, 검날, 검집, 보석의 4개로 분해되어 있는 상태이며, 이 모든 부위를 모아 검으로 완성되면 고대의 비밀을 지닌 검이 된다고 하네요. 현재 검자루에 적힌 암호를 통해 검날이 있는 위치를 찾았어요. 이 검날을 가져와주세요. 검날은 벨라도 성지에 봉인되어 있어요."
20350	"일전에 획득한 목걸이를 분석하던 중에 이 목걸이에 독특한 장치가 되어 있다는 것을 알게 되었습니다. 아마도 이 목걸이는 2개로 나뉘어져있는 것 같습니다. 그래서 2개의 목걸이를 합치면 본래 주인의 이니셜을 확일 할 수 있을 것입니다. 네? 이것과 같은 목걸이를 가지고 계신다구요? 그럼 그 목걸이를 줘보세요. 그 목걸이를 합쳐 이 노예상인들을 부린 사람이 누군지 알아야겠습니다. 어디보자…이니셜은 G.M…G.M이라….아…G.M이라면 제국의 대부호인 기아모프를 말하는 것 아닐까요? 일단은 기아모프를 생포하여 사실 여부를 가려야 할 것 같습니다. 이제 저희와 함께 기아모프를 만나러 가보시죠. 기아모프는 현재 보누스 숲의 별장에서 지내고 있다고 합니다."
20351	"제길! 그들의 사병들 때문에 기아모프를 사로잡지 못했습니다. 이제 그는 그의 막대한 부를 이용하여 더 많은 사병과 더 안전한 곳으로 숨어버릴겁니다. 저희는 이제부터 기아모프가 어느 곳으로 이동하는지를 추적할 것입니다. 저희가 길드이기는 하자 기아모프가 부리는 사병만큼의 숫자를 감당하긴 힘들 것입니다. 그러니 앞으로도 저희와 함께 싸워주시길 부탁드립니다."
20352	"휴식의 비약을 제조하기 위해서는 유황과 만드레이크가 다량으로 필요해요.또한 콘티구스 지역에서 생활중인 얄루 야만족들이 제조하는 독특한 물이 필요해요. 이 물은 물에 담겨있는 것을 몸에 흡수시키는 성질이 뛰어나서 유황과 만드레이크로 제조학 약을 몸에 확실히 받아들일수 있도록하는 작용이 있답니다. 저희가 보관중인 것을 사용하기 어려우니 직접 재료를 모아다주세요.  "
20353	"재료를 모두 모아오셨군요. 잠시만 기다려주세요. 재료를 다 모아오실 때가 되어서 미리 만들 준비를 시켜두어서 만드는데 얼마 걸리지 않을거예요. 병사들을 생각하는 성주라 요즘에 보기드문 성품을 지니셨네요. 아! 이제 제조가 다 된 모양이네요. 너무 빨리 만들어져서 조금 당황하셨겠지만 저희 고대문명 클랜에는 여러분이 생각지 못하는 다양한 방식들을 통해서 약을 제조할 수 있답니다. 그럼 병사들과 즐거운 하루를 보내세요~"
20354	"비약을 마신 병사들은 잠시동안이지만 정말로 황홀한 휴식을 즐길 수 있었고, 병사들은 당신의 마음씀씀이에 감동하여 사기가 올랐다."
20355	"이제 검날을 얻었으니 검자루와 합쳐 다음의 부위가 어디있는지 알아 낼 수 있을거예요. 이제 저희는 이 검의 해석에 들어갈거예요. 해석이 끝나는대로 당신에 연락을 드릴게요. "
20356	"현재 우리 길드에서 제작된 붉은 강철이 약탈당하고있다는 정보가 들어왔다. 현재 다수의 장소에서 약탈을 당하고 있기에 길드내의 인원만으로 약탈을 막아내기에는 불가능하여, 그대에게 도움을 요청하고자 한다. 현재 프레푸젠치 쪽에서 붉은 강철을 약탈 당했다는정보가 들어왔다. 이 프레푸젠치 진입로로 가서 붉은 강철을 회수해주길 바란다."
20357	"그대의 도움으로 붉은 강철이 완전히 약탈 당하는 것은 막을 수 있었다. 감사하게 생각한다. 다만 붉은 강철을 약탈한 것이 단순한 산적이 아니라 일종의 작전을 지시받은 부대와 같았다는 점에서는 의구심이 드는것은 확실하다. 이 문제에 대해서는 우리가 좀 더 면밀하게 살펴 볼 것이다. "
20358	"어서오세요. 이번엔 다름이 아니라 저희와 친하게 지내고 있던 엔트들이 난폭해지는 일이 일어나서요. 아마도 이번 일과 같은 일을 해결하신 적이 있다는 소문을 들었거든요. 그래서 부탁드려요. 엔트들이 난폭해진 원인을 알아봐주세요."
20359	"흠 이것이 엔트들을 난폭하게 만든 원인이란 말이죠. 알겠어요. 이 분노의 핵에 대해서는 저희 쪽에서도 알아보도록 할게요. 난폭해진 엔트들을 도와주셔서 감사해요."
20360	"아 왔나! 저번에 있었던 전투에서 획득한 분노의 핵에 대한 조사가 어느정도 진척되어서 연락했다! 분노의 핵은 어떤 물질은 연금술을 통해서 만들어낸 것으로 보인다! 그리하여 우리 길드에서는 그 이드마크라는 자의 연구실을 찾는 것에 집중했지. 그래서 이드마크의 연구소가 엑실리스의 지역의 어딘가에 있다는 것은 알아내었다! 자네의 역할은 이 엑실리스 지역 어딘가에 있는 이드마크의 연구소를 찾아 주는 것이다!"
20361	"이것이 어떤 문서인지는 모르나 분명 이드마크가 무엇을 위해 행동하는지의 단서정도는 잡을 수 있을 것이다. 이제부터 우리 길드는 이 문서의 해석과 이드마크의 추적에 들어가겠다. 수고했다!"
20362	"오 왔어? 이번에 너희에게 줄 의뢰는 바로 이것! 이 사람, 오드로프를 조용히 처리하는게 이번 의뢰야. 왜 이사람을 제거해야되는지, 무슨 일을 했는지에 대해선 알려줄 수 없어. 알잖아? 우리 까마귀 클랜이 이런 곳이란거. 그럼 잘부탁해~"
20363	"아 의뢰는 여전히 확실히 완수하는구나. 이것으로 의뢰는 완료. 이번에도 수고했어."
20364	"용암지대의 더위를 막아줄 차가운 기운을 내뿜는 보석이라…예전에 아스트렐란치의 보석지대에 그런 보석이 발굴된 기록이 남아있군요. 대부분의 보석은 유황을 나르는 제국군에게 지급되었고…일부는 아스트렐란치의 야만족들에게 약탈 당했다고 합니다. 이런 내용을 보면 제국군이나 아스트렐란치의 야만족들을 통해 얻으시는게 제일 빠른 길인거 같습니다."

//             서브퀘스트
25000	"Remove Barbarians"
25001	"Imperial's scout discovery"
25002	"The location of assassin"
25003	"Assassin troops of arcane snifer"
25004	"Suspicious movement"
25005	"Catch horse riding unit"
25006	"Enemy's base"
25007	"Sweep the enemy's base"
25008	"Sweep the gang of bandits"
25009	"Gang of bandits's base"
25010	"Sweep the gang of bandits's base"
25011	"Secure tree"
25012	"Removal of danger"
25013	"Training of close soldier"
25014	"Training of long range soldier"
25015	"Training of speed soldier"
25016	"Crow Clan Support "
25017	"Flame Clan Support "
25018	"Iron Lord Clan Support"
25019	"Liberty Alliance Clan Support"
25020	"Ancient civilizations Clan Support"
25021	"Crow Clan's rquest"
25022	"Occupy Jewel mine"
25023	"Ancient civilizations Clan's request"
25024	"Battle with theif"
25025	"Minotaur Hell training"
25026	"Cyclope training"
25027	"Big Lycan training"
25028	"Ancient civilizations Clan's request"
25029	"Battle with theif"
25030	"Flame Clan's request"
25031	"Remove the Evil Monster"
25032	"Anger Core"
25033	"Protect mine"
25034	"Battle with Imperial's troop"
25035	"Get a head start"
25036	"letter of Liberty Alliance"
25037	"The last of the gang of bandits"
25038	"Bomber discovery"
25039	"Bomber removal"
25040	"Ready to party"
25041	"Carnival alcohol"
25042	"Carnival firecracker"
25043	"Iron Lord Clan's request"
25044	"Remove Corrupted Imperials"
25045	"Get the Ten year ginseng"
25046	"The water is for boil down Ten year ginseng"
25047	"Boil down Ten year ginseng"
25048	"Nutritious tonic"
25049	"Collect Mandrake "
25050	"Find firewood"
25051	"Evil Monster's blood"
25052	"Find a treasure map"
25053	"Treasure map's piece"
25054	"Treasure "
25055	"Magma Golem's energy"
25056	"Ancient Ent's call"
25057	"Ancient Ent's request"
25058	"Elite Imperials"
25059	"Infectious diseases"
25060	"Fallen angel's request"
25061	"Fake fallen Angel"
25062	"Magma Golem training"
25063	"Ancient Ent training"
25064	"Fallen Angel training"
25065	"New blacksmith's challenge"
25066	"Collect Iron"
25067	"Get Flame"
25068	"Meet the blacksmith"
25069	"메디우스 평야탐색"
25070	"메디우스 산맥탐색"
25071	"메디우스 경계지역탐색"
25072	"메디우스 강 유역탐색"
25073	"메디우스 호수탐색"
25074	"아스트렐란치 경계지역탐색"
25075	"아스트렐란치 보석지대탐색"
25076	"아스트렐란치 중앙광산탐색"
25077	"아스트렐란치 계곡탐색"
25078	"콘티구스 강 유역탐색"
25079	"콘티구스 용암지탐색"
25080	"콘티구스 화산지탐색"
25081	"콘티구스 황야탐색"
25082	"보누스 만드레이크 밭탐색"
25083	"보누스 숲탐색"
25084	"보누스 대로탐색"
25085	"벨라도 진입로탐색"
25086	"벨라도 성지탐색"
25087	"벨라도 숲탐색"
25088	"프레푸젠치 진입로탐색"
25089	"프레푸젠치 광산탐색"
25090	"엑실리스 유황지대탐색"
25091	"엑실리스 평원탐색"
25092	"엑실리스 벌판탐색"
25093	"코피오수스 진입로탐색"
25094	"코피오수스 산림지탐색"
25095	"코피오수스 만드레이크 밭탐색"
25096	"코피오수스 산맥탐색"
25097	"코피오수스 벌판탐색"
25098	"코피오수스 대로탐색"
25099	"레부스 골짜기탐색"
25100	"성지 레부스탐색"
25101	"레부스 산탐색"
25102	"콘주투 산탐색"
25103	"콘주투 홀탐색"
25104	"콘주투 강 유역탐색"
25105	"락수스 진입로탐색"
25106	"락수스 용암지탐색"
25107	"락수스 유황지탐색"
25108	"락수스 휴화산 지역탐색"
25109	"락수스 깊은 곳탐색"
25110	"앰플로 강 유역탐색"
25111	"앰플로 대로탐색"
25112	"앰플로 만드레이크 밭탐색"
25113	"엠플로 숲탐색"
25114	"유황 약탈하기"
25115	"유황 수집하기"
25116	"유황 지대의 야만족"
25117	"차가운 보석"
25118	"차가운 보석 찾기"
25119	"고대문명 클랜 방문"
25120	"고대의 지도 수집"
25121	"의뢰완수"
25122	"고대문명 클랜 방문"
25123	"옛 유물이 봉인된 곳"
25124	"의뢰완수"
25125	"정체불명의 집단"
25126	"성 보강"
25127	"버려진 부대 구출"
25128	"콘티구스에서의 힘"
25129	"콘티구스의 세력견제"
25130	"까마귀 방문2"
25131	"범인의 흔적 찾기"
25132	"찾아낸 범인"
25133	"의뢰완수"
25134	"백병전의 메달 수집"
25135	"저격수의 메달 수집"
25136	"암살자의 마패 수집"
25137	"불꽃 클랜 방문"
25138	"마물 부대의 침공"
25139	"마물 부대의  지휘자"
25140	"지휘자의 정체"
25141	"지휘자 퇴치"
25142	"아쉬운 결과"
25143	"시간의 보옥 모으기"
25144	"만드레이크 수집"
25145	"자유동맹 방문"
25146	"노예시장 찾기"
25147	"노예시장 분쇄"
25148	"자유의 기쁨"
25149	"고대문명 클랜 방문"
25150	"봉인된 장소 탐색"
25151	"탁본 회수"
25152	"보석 수집2"
25153	"보누스 대로 순찰"
25154	"강철 군주 방문"
25155	"만드레이크 수집"
25156	"의뢰완수"
25157	"벨라도 진입로의 산적"
25158	"성 공격"
25159	"고대문명 클랜 방문"
25160	"검날이 봉인된 장소"
25161	"검날과 자루"
25162	"소독에 쓸 유황 수집"
25163	"목걸의 비밀"
25164	"목걸이의 주인"
25165	"자유동맹 방문"
25166	"고대 문명 클랜 방문"
25167	"휴식의 비약 재료 수집"
25168	"휴식의 비약 재료 수집2"
25169	"고대 문명 클랜 방문"
25170	"병사들에게 휴식을"
25171	"벨라도 숲의 적들"
25172	"강철 군주 방문"
25173	"붉은 강철 회수"
25174	"약탈단"
25175	"의뢰완수"
25176	"백병전의 메달 수집"
25177	"저격수의 메달 수집"
25178	"암살자의 마패 수집"
25179	"프레푸젠치 광산 점령"
25180	"보석 수집3"
25181	"프레푸젠치 무법자들"
25182	"유황 수집하기2"
25183	"마그마 골렘 퇴치"
25184	"타락 창병"
25185	"고대문명 클랜 방문"
25186	"난폭해진 엔트"
25187	"의뢰완수"
25188	"성주들 견제"
25189	"나무수집"
25190	"불꽃 클랜 방문"
25191	"이드마크의 연구실"
25192	"이드마크의 연구"
25193	"분노의 핵의 비밀"
25194	"엑실리스 정찰"
25195	"코피우스 진입로 진출"
25196	"까마귀 방문"
25197	"제거 대상 찾기"
25198	"제거"
25199	"의뢰완수"
25200	"코피우스 진입로의 산적"

//서브 퀘스트 설명
27000	"You have to stabilize around. Please remove Barbarians around castle."
27001	"There is the Imperial troops in Medius mountain"
27002	"Remove enemy's troops in #what#"
27003	"Remove the Arcane snifer troops"
27004	"Remove enemy arround castle"
27005	"Please remove horse riding units around castle"
27006	"Scout the base"
27007	"Remove the base"
27008	"Remove enemies arround castle"
27009	"Scout the gang of bandits's base"
27010	"Remove the gang of bandits's base"
27011	"Collect wood"
27012	"Attack the castle "
27013	"Collect close medal"
27014	"Collect long distance medal"
27015	"Collect speed medal"
27016	"Collect Crow Clan's Tokens "
27017	"Collect Flame Clan's Tokens "
27018	"Collect Iron Lord Clan's Tokens "
27019	"Collect Liberty Alliance Clan's Tokens "
27020	"Collect Ancient civilizations Clan's Tokens "
27021	"Collect red Iron"
27022	"Jewel mine occupation"
27023	"Grave robber reconnaissance"
27024	"Grave robber removal"
27025	"Battle with Minotaur Hell"
27026	"Battle with Cyclope"
27027	"Battle with Big Lycan"
27028	"Scout the theif"
27029	"Remove the thief"
27030	"Visit Flame Clan"
27031	"Remove the Evil Monster"
27032	"Get Anger Core "
27033	"Mine occupation"
27034	"Remove Elite Imperials"
27035	"Attack the castle "
27036	"Remove the gang of bandits"
27037	"Remove the last gang of bandits troops"
27038	"Bomber reconnaissance"
27039	"Bomber removal"
27040	"Get Minotaur Hell meat"
27041	"Collect Mandrake"
27042	"Collect sulfur"
27043	"Scout Corrupted Imperials"
27044	"Remove Corrupted Imperials"
27045	"Get Ten year ginseng "
27046	"Get Sulfur water"
27047	"Remove enemies at Mandrake"
27048	"Visit wise man"
27049	"Collect Mandrake"
27050	"Collect  wood"
27051	"Get Evil Monster's blood"
27052	"Get Treasure map"
27053	"Get torn treasure map"
27054	"Remove the gang of bandits in treasure area"
27055	"Collect sulfur"
27056	"Visit Ancient Ent forest"
27057	"Remove Imperials"
27058	"Remove Elite Imperials"
27059	"Remove Fallen Angel "
27060	"Remove Imperial army "
27061	"Remove Fallen Angel "
27062	"Battle with Magma Golem"
27063	"Battle with Ancient Ent"
27064	"Battle with Fallen Angel"
27065	"Meet the new blacksmith."
27066	"Collect Iron"
27067	"Please get Flame through battle"
27068	"Return to Blacksmith"
27069	"메디우스 평야를 탐색하자."
27070	"메디우스 산맥을 탐색하자."
27071	"메디우스 경계지역을 탐색하자."
27072	"메디우스 강 유역을 탐색하자."
27073	"메디우스 호수를 탐색하자."
27074	"아스트렐란치 경계지역을 탐색하자."
27075	"아스트렐란치 보석지대를 탐색하자."
27076	"아스트렐란치 중앙광산을 탐색하자."
27077	"아스트렐란치 계곡을 탐색하자."
27078	"콘티구스 강 유역을 탐색하자."
27079	"콘티구스 용암지를 탐색하자."
27080	"콘티구스 화산지를 탐색하자."
27081	"콘티구스 황야를 탐색하자."
27082	"보누스 만드레이크 밭을 탐색하자."
27083	"보누스 숲을 탐색하자."
27084	"보누스 대로를 탐색하자."
27085	"벨라도 진입로를 탐색하자."
27086	"벨라도 성지를 탐색하자."
27087	"벨라도 숲을 탐색하자."
27088	"프레푸젠치 진입로를 탐색하자."
27089	"프레푸젠치 광산을 탐색하자."
27090	"엑실리스 유황지대를 탐색하자."
27091	"엑실리스 평원을 탐색하자."
27092	"엑실리스 벌판을 탐색하자."
27093	"코피오수스 진입로를 탐색하자."
27094	"코피오수스 산림지를 탐색하자."
27095	"코피오수스 만드레이크 밭을 탐색하자."
27096	"코피오수스 산맥을 탐색하자."
27097	"코피오수스 벌판을 탐색하자."
27098	"코피오수스 대로를 탐색하자."
27099	"레부스 골짜기를 탐색하자."
27100	"성지 레부스를 탐색하자."
27101	"레부스 산을 탐색하자."
27102	"콘주투 산을 탐색하자."
27103	"콘주투 홀을 탐색하자."
27104	"콘주투 강 유역을 탐색하자."
27105	"락수스 진입로를 탐색하자."
27106	"락수스 용암지를 탐색하자."
27107	"락수스 유황지를 탐색하자."
27108	"락수스 휴화산 지역을 탐색하자."
27109	"락수스 깊은 곳을 탐색하자."
27110	"앰플로 강 유역을 탐색하자."
27111	"앰플로 대로를 탐색하자."
27112	"앰플로 만드레이크 밭을 탐색하자."
27113	"엠플로 숲을 탐색하자."
27114	"콘티구스 강 유역에서 유황을 약탈하고 있는 유황수송대를 퇴치하자"
27115	"유황을 수집하자."
27116	"콘티구스 강 유역에서 생활하는 야만족들의 무차별적인 공격을 막기 위해 그들을 퇴치하자."
27117	"용암지대의 더위를 막을 차가운 보석의 위치를 현자에게 물어보자"
27118	"아스트렐란치의 보석지대 주변의 누군가가 차가운 보석을 지니고 있다고 한다. 적들을 퇴치하여 차가운 보석을 획득하자."
27119	"고대 문명 클랜을 방문해보자."
27120	"어딘가로 흩어졌을 고대의 지도를 수집하자"
27121	"고대 문명 클랜을 방문하여 의뢰를 완수하자."
27122	"저번에 찾아준 지도의 해석이 끝났다고 한다. 찾아가보자."
27123	"콘티구스 용암지에 있는 봉인의 장소를 돌파하자."
27124	"봉인의 장소에서 획득한 칼자루를 건내주자."
27125	"정체불명의 집단이 고대문명 클랜 주변에 모여들고 있다. 이들을 처리하자."
27126	"성벽의 보강을 위해 유황과 철을 수집하자."
27127	"콘티구스 화산지에 버려진 부대를 구출하라."
27128	"콘티구스에서 아군이 더 이상 피해받지 않도록 주변의 적들을 처리하자."
27129	"콘티구스에 있는 성주들의 세력을 견재하기 위해 그들의 성을 빼앗자."
27130	"까마귀 클랜에 방문하자."
27131	"의뢰인을 살해한 범인을 찾기 위해 주변 적들로부터 정보를 획득하자"
27132	"범인 어떤 용병 부대의 사람으로 용병들과 함께 있다. 그들을 퇴치하자."
27133	"까마귀 클랜을 방문하여 의뢰를 완수하자."
27134	"근접 병력의 힘을 키우기 위해 백병전의 메달을 수집하자."
27135	"원거리 병력의 힘을 키우기 위해 저격수의 메달을 수집하자."
27136	"기동 병력의 힘을 키우기 위해 암살자의 마패를 수집하자."
27137	"불꽃 클랜으로 부터 연락이 왔다. 불꽃 클랜을 방문해보자."
27138	"마물의 부대를 발견했다. 그들을 처리하자."
27139	"마물 부대를 이용하여 침공한 지휘관을 찾아야 한다. 근처의 적들을 통해 정보를 수집하자."
27140	"황제군 중 하나가 정찰 도중 마물에게 수상한 짓을 한 어떤 인물을 보았다고 한다. 그에게 정보를 듣자."
27141	"지휘자는 이드마크라고 하는 연금술사다. 그의 부대를 물리치고 그를 사로잡자."
27142	"이드마크를 사로잡는데는 실패했지만 그의 부대는 퇴치했다. 불꽃 클랜으로 돌아가자."
27143	"다른 성주의 성을 공략하여 짧은 시간의 보옥을 모으자."
27144	"만드레이크 밭에서 만드레이크를 수집하자."
27145	"자유동맹으로 부터 연락이 왔다. 자유동맹을 방문하자."
27146	"주변의 적들로부터 노예시장의 위치를 알아내자."
27147	"노예시장은 용병들이 지키고 있다. 이 용병들을 처리하자."
27148	"대부분의 노예들이 자유의 몸이 되었다. 자유동맹을 방문하여 이야기를 나누자."
27149	"고대문명 클랜으로부터 연락이 왔다. 고대문명 클랜을 방문하자"
27150	"이전에 탐험한 봉인된 장소에 검자루의 봉인을 해제할 수 있는 힌트가 있을 것이다. 다시한번 탐험해보자."
27151	"봉인된 장소에 고대 언어로 적힌 석판의 탁본을 만들었다. 이제 고대문명 클랜으로 돌아가자."
27152	"보석을 수집하자"
27153	"보누스 대로를 순찰하여 보누수 대로를 안전한 곳으로 만들자."
27154	"강철 군주 클랜으로 부터 연락이 왔다. 강철 군주를 방문하자."
27155	"붉은 강철을 만드는데 필요한 만드레이크를 수집하자."
27156	"붉은 강철을 만드는데 필요한 만드레이크를 모두 수집했다. 강철군주 클랜으로 돌아가 의뢰를 완수하자."
27157	"벨라도 진입로 주변에 산적들이 판을 치고 있다. 이들을 처리하자."
27158	"다른 성주의 성을 공격하자."
27159	"고대문명 클랜으로부터 연락이 왔다. 고대문명 클랜을 방문하자"
27160	"검날이 봉인되어있는 장소는 마물들이 지키고 있다. 마물을 처리하고 검날을 획득하자."
27161	"고대문명 클랜으로 돌아가 검날과 자루를 합쳐보자."
27162	"소독에 사용될 유황을 수집하자."
27163	"일전에 구한 목걸이에 특수한 장치가 되어있는 것을 발견했다고 한다. 자유동맹을 찾아가보자."
27164	"목걸이의 장치를 통해서 목걸이의 주인이 누구인지 알아냈다. 제국의 대부호 기아모프다. 그의 사병들을 처리하고 그를 사로잡자."
27165	"기아모프를 사로잡는데는 실패했다. 자유동맹을 방문하여 앞으로 일에 대해 의논하자."
27166	"고대문명 클랜이 가지고 있는 휴식의 비약에 대한 정보를 물으러 고대문명 클랜을 방문하자"
27167	"휴식의 비약의 재료가 되는 유황과 만드레이크를 획득하자."
27168	"얄루 야만족이 생산하는 독특한 물을 획득하자"
27169	"모든 재료를 수집했다. 이제 고대문명 클랜으로 돌아가 비약을 제조하자."
27170	"성으로 돌아가 병사들에게 휴식의 비약을 나누어주자."
27171	"벨라도 숲에 있는 적들을 처리하여 그들의 활동을 줄이자."
27172	"강철 군주 클랜으로 부터 연락이 왔다. 강철 군주를 방문하자."
27173	"강철 군주에서 제작한 붉은 강철이 약탈당했다. 프레푸젠치 진입로에서 붉은 강철을 회수하자"
27174	"붉은 강철을 회수하자, 붉은 강철을 약탈한 녀석들이 나타났다. 처리하자."
27175	"붉은 강철은 모두 회수했다. 강철군주 클랜으로 돌아가 의뢰를 완수하자."
27176	"근접 병력의 힘을 키우기 위해 백병전의 메달을 수집하자."
27177	"원거리 병력의 힘을 키우기 위해 저격수의 메달을 수집하자."
27178	"기동 병력의 힘을 키우기 위해 암살자의 마패를 수집하자."
27179	"프레푸젠치 광산을 점령하자."
27180	"보석을 수집하자"
27181	"프레푸젠치에서 약탈을 일삼는 무법자들을 처리하자."
27182	"유황을 수집하자."
27183	"엑실리스 유황지대에 있는 마그마골렘을 퇴치하자"
27184	"엑실리스 유황지대에 있는 타락한 신성창병들을 퇴치하자"
27185	"고대문명 클랜에서 연락이 왔다. 고대문명 클랜을 방문하자."
27186	"갑작스럽게 난폭해진 엔트들을 처리하자."
27187	"난폭해진 엔트들을 처리하고, 분노의 핵을 획득했다. 고대문명 클랜으로 돌아가 의뢰를 완수하자."
27188	"성주들의 견제가 심해지고 있다. 성들을 점령하여 그들의 견제를 방해하자."
27189	"나무를 수집하자"
27190	"불꽃 클랜으로 부터 연락이 왔다. 불꽃 클랜을 방문해보자."
27191	"엑실리스의 지역의 야만족과 제국군으로 부터 이드마크의 연구실의 위치를 알아내자."
27192	"이드마크의 연구실의 위치를 알아냈다. 이드마크의 연구실로 향하자."
27193	"분노의 핵에 대한 내용이 적힌것 같은 문서를 찾아냈다. 불꽃 클랜으로 가져가보자."
27194	"엑실리스 지역을 정찰하자."
27195	"코피우스 진입로로 진출하는 동안 성의 방어를 위해 미리 적의 성들을 점령해두자"
27196	"까마귀 클랜으로부터 연락이 왔다. 까마귀 클랜을 방문하자."
27197	"제거 대상이 알아차릴수 없도록 정보를 알고 있을 3개의 부대를 공략하자."
27198	"제거 대상의 위치를 알아냈다. 대상을 제거하자."
27199	"까마귀 클랜을 방문하여 의뢰를 완수하자."
27200	"코피우스 진입로 주변에 산적이 출몰한다고 한다. 그들을 처리하자."
29999	"Quest Reservation"

// 유닛이름
30000	"Holy Spearman"
30001	"Arcane snifer"
30002	"Flame Knights"
30003	"Minotaur Hell"
30004	"Cyclope"
30005	"Big Lycan"
30006	"Magma Golem"
30007	"Ancient Ent"
30008	"Fallen Angel"
30009	"The Vatican's Holy spearman was trained to protect religionism. Because they are religious, they do not know fear by God's name. Since armor is too heavy and thick, they had a highly defense power and slow speed. They belongs to the small unit and strong to the speed unit or fallen angel. 
Advantage to: Fallen Angel, Flame Knights, Big Lycan
Disadvantage to: Cyclope, Arcane sniper"
30010	"The Sniper Archers of elite were trained on the Arcane Magic. The enemies can't see them because they use lce magic arrow at long distance.They belongs to the small long distance unit and strong to slow unit. Especially they strong to Magma Golem and Elemental resistance.
Advantage to: Magma Golem, Holy spearman
Disadvantage to: Big Lycan, Flame Knights."
30011	"The Vatican soldiers has become terror to devils by spear of Holy Ghost flame. They belongs to the small speed unit and strong to long range enemies by high speed.
Advantage to: Ancient Ent, Arcane sniper, Cyclope
Disadvantage to: Minotaur Hell, Holy spearman, Magma Golem"
30012	"They are the horrible units from hell and who make blooded battlefield using strong strength and ax. They belongs to the midsize unit and strong to speed unit or small unit.
Advantage to: Flame Knights, Big Lycan, Holy spearman
Disadvantage to: Ancient Ent, Arcane sniper."
30013	"They are one of the unnoticeable Cycolpe group because they live in a high rock mountain. The best feature of the Cycolpe is big eye, they are sweep the battlefield by ultra high temperature laser. The peoples call them Evil eye and they believe that when their eyes met, die in fear. They belongs to the midsize long range unit and strong to Holly Spearman.
Advantage to: Holy spearman, Minotaur Hell
Disadvantage to: Fallen Angel, Big Lycan"
30014	"They are the branch of werewolves tribe and they are being called Big Lycan because they had big body than normal werewolves. Compared to their big body, they are fast and rip the enemies by strong claw. Also, big Lycan have poison, If you touch that claw, the poison spreads to body and die. They belongs to the midsize speed unit and strong to Archer.
Advantage to: Arcane sniper, Cyclope
Disadvantage to: Magma Golem, Minotaur Hell"
30015	"They was born from hot lava who has strong defense power because their epidermis has solidified massively than Iron. Because of their epidermis, the lycan's tooth and claw attack is impotent. They had strong defense power and  strength but speed is slow. They are strong to hand to hand combat and they are specialized unit for defense.
Advantage to: Big Lycan, Flame Knights
Disadvantage to: Arcane sniper, Ancient Ent"
30016	"The spirit of tree has lived where the sun doesn't shine for tens of thousands of years. They didn't move well but when their forest is in danger, attack the invaders. They can easily throw around rock who have strong powers. They belongs to the large range unit and strong to slow unit of close range.
Advantage to: Minotaur Hell, Magma Golem
Disadvantage to: Flame Knights, Big Lycan, fallen angel"
30017	"The Fallen angels and boss were uprooted from their country due to the revolt. The Fallen angel is a complete unknown but they works independently and use a strong bigger sword. They belongs to the large speed unit and strong to large unit of close range.
Advantage to: Cyclope, Ancient Ent
Disadvantage to: Holy spearman, Magma Golem"


// 스팟이름
30100	"Barbarians"
30101	"gang of bandits"
30102	"Impire scouting"
30103	"Impire guards"
30104	"Imperials's the First corps leader"
30105	"Impire guard troops"
30106	"Hidden Sulfur cave"
30107	"Secret maze cave in Bellado forest"
30108	"Magma Golem appear region"
30109	"Ancient Ent forest"
30110	"Lost ancient Ritual place"
30111	"Fallen Angel nest"
30112	"God's Sanctuary"
30113	"Deep in the forest caveDeep in the forest cave"
30114	"Suspicious structure"


// 
35000	"Arcane snifer troops"
35001	"Horse riding Imperials"
35002	"Horse riding Elite Imperials"
35003	"Banditry's base"
35004	"Grave robber"
35005	"Mystery troops"


//지역이름
39000	"Around castle"
39001	"Medius ravine "
39002	"Medius plain"
39003	"Medius mountain"
39004	"Medius lake"
39005	"Astrellranch jewel zone"
39006	"Astrellranch main mine"
39007	"Astrellranch valley"
39008	"Contigus basin"
39009	"Contigus malpais"
39010	"Contigus volcanic zone"
39011	"Contigus wilderness"
39012	"Bonus mandrake field"
39013	"Bonus forest"
39014	"Bonus main street"
39015	"Bellado access road"
39016	"bellado Holy Land"
39017	"Bellado forest"
39018	"Praepujench access road"
39019	"Praepujench mine"
39020	"Eksillease sulfur zone"
39021	"Eksillease plain"
39022	"Eksillease field"
39023	"Kopiosus access road"
39024	"Kopiosus forest"
39025	"Kopiosus mandrake field"
39026	"Kopiosus mountain"
39027	"Kopiosus field"
39028	"Kopiosus main street"
39029	"Lebuus ravine "
39030	"Holy Land lebuus"
39031	"Lebuus mountain"
39032	"Konjutou mountain"
39033	"Konjutou hole"
39034	"Konjutou basin"
39035	"Laksuss access road"
39036	"Laksuss malpais"
39037	"Laksuss sulfur zone"
39038	"Laksuss dormant volcano zone"
39039	"Deep in a laksuss "
39040	"Amplro basin"
39041	"Amplro main street"
39042	"Amplro Mandrake field"
39043	"Amplro forest"
39044	"Medius bridge"
39045	"Medius canyon"
39046	"Medius boundary area"
39047	"Medius basin"
39048	"Astrellranch area"


// 아이템
40000	"Long sword"
40001	"Two-Hand Sword"
40002	"Giant Sword"
40003	"Crooked sword"
40004	"Rune sword"
40005	"Longbow"
40006	"Leather Long Bow"
40007	"Flat bow"
40008	"Composite Bow"
40009	"Wing Bow"
40010	"Wood spear"
40011	"Spear"
40012	"Long spear"
40013	"Large long spear"
40014	"Rune spear"
40015	"Wood stick"
40016	"Walking stick"
40017	"Oak stick"
40018	"White wood stick"
40019	"Wand"
40020	"Wood helmet"
40021	"Iron helmet"
40022	"Steel helmet"
40023	"Plate helmet"
40024	"Orichalcum helmet"
40025	"Wood armor"
40026	"Iron armor"
40027	"Steel armor"
40028	"Plate armor"
40029	"Orichalcum armor"
40030	"Wood boots"
40031	"Iron boots"
40032	"Steel boots"
40033	"Plate boots"
40034	"Orichalcum boots"
40035	"Wood necklace"
40036	"Iron necklace"
40037	"Silver necklace"
40038	"Anger Core"
40039	"Minotaur Hell meat"
40040	"Ten year ginseng"
40041	"Sulfur water"
40042	"Evil Monster blood"
40043	"Treasure map"
40044	"Treasure map piece"
40045	"Flame"
40046	"Fallen shard"
40047	"Labyrinth treasure map piece"
40048	"Minotaur Hell ring"
40049	"Cyclope ring"
40050	"Big Lycan ring"
40051	"Magma Golem ring"
40052	"Ancient Ent ring"
40053	"Fallen Angel ring"
40054	"Big Lycan's secret area map"
40055	"Cross necklace"
40056	"Gold necklace"
40057	"Gold key"
40058	"Magic whistle"
40059	"VIP tiket"
40060	"The first relic"
40061	"The second relic"
40062	"The third relic"
40063	"The fourth relic"
40064	"The fifth relic"
40065	"The sixth relic"
40066	"The seventh relic"
40067	"Freedom Watch"
40068	"Iron Compass"
40069	"Collected weapon"
40070	"Lost smith's armor"
41000	"Increase drop"
41001	"Increase resource acquisition"
41002	"The acquisition of booty have doubled after battle. This effect last for an hour."
41003	"The acquisition of booty have doubled after battle. This effect last for an hour."
41004	"arondite"
41005	"failnot"
41006	"longinus spear"
41007	"calradbolg"
41008	"sword of lee"
41009	"barsai_sword"
41010	"clausolas"
41011	"brunak"
41012	"ge zerg"
41013	"asclepion"
41014	"gangnam armor"
41015	"nemea lion armor"
41016	"mananan armor"
41017	"hildegrim helm"
41018	"firerat helm"
41019	"egir helm"
41020	"infinite boots"
41021	"yarngrape"
41022	"talaria"
41023	"kundala"
41024	"harmonia necklace"
41025	"bronze bell"
41026	"범인의 목걸이"
41027	"노예시장에서 획득한 목걸이"
41028	"고대의 지도 조각"
41029	"휴식의 비약"
41030	"얄루족의 물"
41031	"붉은 강철"
41032	"고대의 검자루"
41033	"고대의 검날"
41034	"힌트가 적힌 탁본"
41035	"이드마크의 문서"
41036	"차가운 보석"

//    아이템 설명
45000	"This is long sword."
45001	"This is huge sword."
45002	"This is bigger sword."
45003	"The sword have difference from person to person."
45004	"The sword was carved Rune letter."
45005	"This is long bow."
45006	"This is leather bow."
45007	"You can make bow using the various woods."
45008	"This is new bow of mechanical design"
45009	"The bow is made of angel's feather."
45010	"This is wood spear."
45011	"This is normal spear. This is better than a wood spear."
45012	"This spear is longer than normal spear. If you can put distance, this is safety."
45013	"This is large spear for battle with trooper."
45014	"The spear was carved Rune letter."
45015	"This is made of magic wood."
45016	"The wooden stick have magical powers."
45017	"The stick is made of magical oak."
45018	"The stick is made of white tree."
45019	"The magician left this wooden stick."
45020	"This helmet is made of wood."
45021	"This helmet is made of Iron."
45022	"This helmet is made of steel. Your head is safety."
45023	"This helmet is made of plate. Your head is heavy."
45024	"This helmet is made of Orichalcum. This is awesome."
45025	"This armor is made of wood. Please use caution."
45026	"This armor is made of Iron. Don't crush this."
45027	"This armor is made of steel. This isn't crush."
45028	"This armor is made of plate. Your body is safety."
45029	"This armor is made of Orichalcum. This is as light as a feather and safety."
45030	"This shoes is made of wood. Please wear thick socks."
45031	"This shoes is made of Iron. This is shiny and awesome."
45032	"This shoes is made of steel. Please endure this weight."
45033	"This shoes is made of plate. Maybe you can't move."
45034	"This shoes is made of Orichalcum. You can run now."
45035	"This necklace is made of wood. Memories are in this."
45036	"This necklace is made of Iron. You can make this."
45037	"This necklace is made of silver. The sapphirine is beautiful."
45038	"This is enigmatic thing and make Evil Monster violently."
45039	"The best-tasting meat is good."
45040	"This precious medicine is variant of mandrake."
45041	"This water mixed sulfur."
45042	"This is Evil Monster's blood."
45043	"This map include treasure's location but this map is torn."
45044	"This is treasure's map piece. You can find treasure location."
45045	"Flame is enough to melt Iron."
45046	"This is Evil Monster's crystal."
45047	"This map include Minotaur Hell's location."
45048	"This Minotaur Hell's ring contracted with you."
45049	"This Cyclope's ring contracted with you."
45050	"This Big Lycan's ring contracted with you."
45051	"This Magma Golem's ring contracted with you."
45052	"This Ancient Ent's ring contracted with you."
45053	"This Fallen Angel's ring contracted with you."
45054	"The Big Lycan is pointing at secret area of hidden ring."
45055	"This is a holy cross necklace. You can feel holy energy."
45056	"This necklace is made of gold. Long times ago, one lord used it."
45057	"You can extend inventory by gold key."
45058	"This whistle can call trader."
45059	"This vip tiket can rearrange trader's item."
45060	"This relic feels strange power."
45061	"This relic feels strange power."
45062	"This relic feels strange power."
45063	"This relic feels strange power."
45064	"This relic feels strange power."
45065	"This relic feels strange power."
45066	"This relic feels strange power."
45067	"This is ancient clock. Maybe the second hand seems to be something wrong."
45068	"Iron Lord Clan used this ancient compass. This isn't indicated the north."
45069	"When the kights saved a princess from fire dragon using this sword. It never wears away."
45070	"Hero tristan used this bow. This bow isn't never miss target."
45071	"The spear is legend that a man who kill god's son using this. If you hurt your body, you'll lose sight."
45072	"Lightning ejects from this noted sword. The edge of knife is spiral shape."
45073	"Eastern countries's hero used this sword. The hero beat the monkey barbarians."
45074	"This sword used for black magic of devil summons. If you hurt your body, maybe you could die."
45075	"King Agateram grabbed this sword. It is called light sword or fire sword that caused a bright flash and blocking view."
45076	"The god of light had this. If you get any blood onto that, make a growl sound."
45077	"Diarmuid of Fianna Knights received the red spear from Ancient Druids. This spear can pierce magic defense."
45078	"The medical god had this stick. That is like a snake coiled that."
45079	"Legend hero Psy wore this armor. The armor is made of silver and stops stale sweat."
45080	"This armor is made of nemea lion's leather. The armor can't hurt the spear or sword."
45081	"Fairy King Manannan wore this gold chain armor. The two jewels light around."
45082	"The hilde and grim had this magic helmet."
45083	"This armor is made of fire mouse's leather. If you wear this, you can fight fire. As it reaches fire, more soft. "
45084	"This is one of the Fafnir dfagon's treasure. There is something magical power."
45085	"The boots edcorated with Infinite gem. If you wear this, you can demonstrate great power."
45086	"God of thunder used this Iron boots."
45087	"God of messenger wore this winged shoes. You can fly in the sky."
45088	"Karna hero wore this earing. The legend of armor and earing is set."
45089	"Kardmos's wife had this necklace. You can enjoy beauty and youth."
45090	"When the Hwanung coming down the sky, received this sacred bell."
45091	"scattered weapons in battlefield."
45092	"Smith's ancestors made this armor. That is an aura of unknown power."
45093	"까마귀 클랜에 의뢰를 했던 의뢰인을 죽인 범인이 흘린 목걸이 입니다."
45094	"노예시장에서 획득한 어디서 본듯한 목걸이입니다."
45095	"무언가 특별한 물건을 가르키는 고대의 지도의 조각입니다."
45096	"짧은 시간에도 확실하게 휴식을 할 수 있게 해주는 고대 문명 클랜의 비약입니다."
45097	"비약에 사용될 얄루족의 독특한 물입니다."
45098	"강철 군주 클랜에서 제작하는 독특한 강철입니다."
45099	"고대의 비밀이 담긴 고대의 검자루입니다."
45100	"고대의 비밀이 담긴 고대 검의 검날입니다. "
45101	"고대의 검자루의 봉인을 풀 수 있는 힌트가 적힌 돌의 탁본입니다."
45102	"이드마크의 연구실에 있던 문서입니다."
45103	"차가운 기운을 내뿜는 신비한 보석입니다."

// xuzhu
45500	"This low-class item is for Holy Spearman and Minotaur Hell, Golem's troops training. You can get probability in castle battlefield."
45501	"This low-class item is for Arcane snifer and Cyclope,Ancient Ent's troops training. You can get probability in castle battlefield."
45502	"This low-class item is for Flame Knights and Big Big Lycan and Fallen Angel's troops training. You can get  probability in castle battlefield."
45503	"This low Bead is for hero's skill Upgrade. You can get low probability in all castle battlefield."
45504	"This exclusive Bead is for hero's skill Upgrade. You can get low probability in over the level 10 castle battlefield."
45505	"This rare Bead is for hero's skill Upgrade. You can get low probability in over the level 15 castle battlefield."
45506	"This hero class Bead is for hero's skill Upgrade. You can get low probability in over the level 20 castle battlefield."
45507	"This legend Bead is for hero's skill Upgrade. You can get low probability in over the level 25 castle battlefield."
45508	"This exclusive item is for Holy Spearman and Minotaur Hell and Magma Golem's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 15 castle battlefield."
45509	"This exclusive item is for Arcane snifer and Cyclope and Ancient Ent's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 15 castle battlefield."
45510	"This exclusive item is for Flame Knights and Big Big Lycan and Fallen Angel's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 15 castle battlefield."
45511	"This rare item is for Holy Spearman and Minotaur Hell and Magma Golem's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 20 castle battlefield."
45512	"This rare item is for Arcane snifer and Cyclope and Ancient Ent's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 20 castle battlefield."
45513	"This rare item is for Flame Knights and Big Big Lycan and Fallen Angel's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 20 castle battlefield."
45514	"This hero class item is for Holy Spearman and Minotaur Hell and Magma Golem's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 30 castle battlefield."
45515	"This hero class item is for Arcane snifer and Cyclope and Ancient Ent's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 30 castle battlefield."
45516	"This hero class item is for Flame Knights and Big Big Lycan and Fallen Angel's troops training. You can get probability in over the level 30 castle battlefield."
45517	"This Strategy Book raise Crow family's hero EXP."
45518	"This Strategy Book raise Iron Lord family's hero EXP."
45519	"This Strategy Book raise Liberty Alliance family's hero EXP."
45520	"This Strategy Book raise Ancient civilizations family's hero EXP."
45521	"This Strategy Book raise Flame family's hero EXP."
45522	"This tokens can change with Crow family's Strategy Book."
45523	"This tokens can change with Iron Lord family's Strategy Book."
45524	"This tokens can change with Liberty Alliance family's Strategy Book."
45525	"This tokens can change with Ancient civilizations family's Strategy Book."
45526	"This tokens can change with Flame family's Strategy Book."

//   기타
50000	"Crow Tokens"
50001	"I.L Tokens"
50002	"L.A Tokens"
50003	"A.C Tokens"
50004	"Flame Tokens"
50010	"Short time bead"
50011	"Bead of time"
50012	"Long time bead"
50013	"hidden bead of time"
50020	"Fighter's Medal"
50021	"Assassin Medal"
50022	"Ranger's Medal"
50023	"Mithril helmet"
50030	"Old feathering"
50031	"Falcon feathering"
50032	"Eagle feathering"
50033	"Griffin feathering"
50040	"Old horseshoe"
50041	"Iron horseshoe"
50042	"Titanium horseshoe"
50043	"Mithril horseshoe"
50050	"Broken horn"
50051	"Strong horn"
50052	"Steel horn"
50053	"Black horn"
50060	"Rotten eyeball"
50061	"Fresh eyeball"
50062	"Beholder's eyeball"
50063	"Devil's eyeball"
50070	"Blunt fang"
50071	"Sharp fang"
50072	"Huge fang"
50073	"Sharp fang"
50080	"Stone shard"
50081	"Magma shard"
50082	"Flame shard"
50083	"Fire of hell's shard"
50090	"Old wood piece"
50091	"Strong piece"
50092	"Lightning wood piece"
50093	"Carved Rune on the wood piece"
50100	"Old feather"
50101	"Nomal feather"
50102	"Angel's feather"
50103	"Black feather"
50300	"Crow Book"
50301	"I.L Book"
50302	"L.A Book"
50303	"A.C Book"
50304	"Flame Book"
51000	"Diamond"


// 패배시 팁
55000	"Please deploy archer troops behind the Holy spearman troops. If the Archer survive longer, you can improve winning rate."
55001	"Please attack the archer troops by fast knight troops. Firstly you have to remove range troops."
55002	"Holy spearman's strength and defense power is good. Please deploy them front line and defend the enemy."
55003	"Holy spearman's speed is slow but their defense power is strong to knights troops."
55004	"The archer troops advantage to the range attack and strong to Holy spearman."
55005	"The fast knights troops are strong to the enemy's archer troops in rear."
55006	"After the battle, please check trough battle statistic which troops had a good war."
55007	"Please deploy troops for resistance. The way arrangement has a big effect on their win."
55008	"Please upgrade hero through exchange Token for the exp book."
55009	"자원이 있으면 끊임없이 영웅을 훈련시키세요. 시간을 들이지 않고도 영웅을 성장시킬수 있는 쉬운 방법입니다."
55010	"방어 유닛인 신성창병, 미노타우르스, 마그마골렘은 원거리 유닛에게 가하는 피해량이 25%감소 합니다."
55011	"원거리 유닛들은 스피드 유닛인 화염기사단, 거대 라이칸, 타천사에게 가하는 피해량이 25%감소 합니다."
55012	"스피드 유닛들은 방어유닛들에게 가하는 피해량이 25%감소합니다."
55013	"소형유닛들은 중형유닛들에게 가하는 피해량이 25%감소합니다."
55014	"중형유닛들은 대형유닛들에게 가하는 피해량이 25%감소합니다."
55015	"대형유닛들은 소형유닛들에게 가하는 피해량이 25%감소합니다."
55016	"무기점에 들러 무기를 바꿔보는건 어떨까요?"
// 접속시 팁
55500	"When you upgrade hero's level, many clan's demand is different. If you don't want resource shortage, have to collect various clan's hero. "
55501	"You can see the jewel mine in 12 level area."
55502	"If you want to get a lot of sulfur, you have to attack the 15 level area's sulfur convoy."
55503	"If you want to get a lot of Mandrake, you have to occupy 19 level area's Mandrake farm."
55504	"If you want to get Medal for troop upgrade, you have to attack the castle."
55505	"If you want to get Bead for skill upgrade, you have to attack the castle."
55506	"You can get various item in Token's battlefield. You can get each clan's token From Monday to Friday. Saturday is Medal and Sunday is Bead."
55507	"Region extension is important to you because you can get new quest and hunting ground."
55508	"Your goal is become strong lord for unity of continent."
55509	"If you get equipment, please use to hero. "
55510	"Minotaur Hell, Cyclope, Big Lycan is midsize and you can meet from 12 level."
55511	"Magma Golem, Ancient Ent, Fallen Angel is big size and you can meet from 12 level."
55512	"If you want to get the gold, please visit to trader"
55513	"The Leader skill can use Specified hero."
55514	"The higher win score, the strong enemy will attack you. "
55515	"가끔 무기상에 방문해 보세요. 매일 강력한 새로운 아이템들을 들여놓는답니다."


//     스킬
60000	"Strength of wolf"
60001	"The hero's troop speed up #ability# for #duration#s."
60002	"Continuous Slash"
60003	"Continuous Slash cause #ability# damage to hero's damage."
60004	"Sweep"
60005	"Sweep cause #ability# damage to enemy's damage."
60006	"Last shooting"
60007	"Last shooting cause #ability#damage to enemy by magic arrow. "
60008	"Fire ball"
60009	"Fire ball shoot huge fire ball to all enemies and cause #ability# damage to them."
60010	"Curse"
60011	"Curse is to reduce #ability# enemy's damage."
60012	"Shield Defence"
60013	"Defense shield is reduce damage for hero's troops for #duration#s."
60014	"Multi shot"
60015	"Multi shot cuase #ability#  damage using arrows."
60016	"Chill blast arrow"
60017	"Chill blast arrow is shooting arrows like a snow ball and cause #ability1# damage, slow down moving speed #ability2# for #duration2#."
60018	"Piercing sting"
60019	"Piercing sting cause #ability# damage to target."
60020	"Moon Slash"
60021	"Moon Slash cause #ability# wide damage to target and enemy by Weapon. Archer puts 30% more damage."
60022	"Surprise attack"
60023	"Surprise attack cause #ability# damage and knock the enemy for 3 seconds."
60024	"Meteor"
60025	"Meteor cause #ability# range damage and knock the enemy for #duration2# seconds."
60026	"Troops Healing"
60027	"Recover the weak army's vitality."
60028	"TEST"
60029	"This is test."
60030	"Hello"
60031	"Hello"
60032	"Increase damage"
60033	"Increase #ability# damage of holy Spearman."
60034	"Penetration "
60035	"Gives defense ignoring damage."
60036	"purification"
60037	"#ability# damage is added to Fallen Angel and Minotaur Hell. Also, damage flame enemyies."
60038	"Increase critical's probability except holy Spearman."
60039	"Increase vitality"
60040	"Increase vitality #ability# for holy spearman."
60041	"Upgrade armor"
60042	"Increase defense #ability# for holy spearman."
60043	"Evasion"
60044	"Reduce the #ability# damage by close attack."
60045	"Smokescreen"
60046	"Reduce normal #ability# damage by long distance attack."
60047	"Hook"
60048	"During the attack from holy spearman, Troops can't move for #duration#s."
60049	"Shield"
60050	"Reduce #ability# damage from long distance attack."
60051	"Self-healing"
60052	"Recover #ability# vitality, every seconds."
60053	"Prayer"
60054	"Increase damage and defense during starting battle. This effect last for #duration#s."
60055	"March"
60056	"Increase #ability# moving speed of holy Spearman."
60057	"Javelin"
60058	"#ability# damage to damage before spear attack."
60059	"Gungnir"
60060	"Increase critical damage with #ability# probability."
60061	"Increase #ability# damage."
60062	"Increase the penetration chance "
60063	"That ignore the defense and #ability# damage to the enemy."
60064	"Increase attack speed"
60065	"Increase #ability# attack speed."
60066	"Quick fire"
60067	"If you have distance with enemy within 20m, increase #ability# attack speed."
60068	"Instant death arrow"
60069	"Instant kill the target with #prob# probability."
60070	"Increase critical probability."
60071	"Increase critical #ability# probability."
60072	"Critical Upgrade"
60073	"Increase #ability# critical damage."
60074	"Small arrow"
60075	"The small arrow fire additional arrow with #prob# probability. Small arrow critical damage to the enemy."
60076	"Close shooting"
60077	"within 10 meters of enemy, increase #ability# critical damage."
60078	"Chill explosion arrow"
60079	"Shoot the Ice explosion arrow with #prob# probability and #ability# damage to enemy, freeze them for #duration#s."
60080	"Chill diffusion"
60081	"Increase range of Chill explosion."
60082	"Chill Upgrade"
60083	"Increase #ability# splash damage of Ice arrow."
60084	"Crushing arrow"
60085	"When attacking to frozen gravel enemy, additional #ability# damage to them."
60086	"Freeze arrow"
60087	"Curdle the enemy with certain probability."
60088	"Increase range"
60089	"Increase range of arrow attack. "
60090	"archer_04"
60091	"promoting spirits"
60092	"When the starting battle, raise the morale and damage #ability#."
60093	"Divine protection"
60094	"When the starting the battle, bless our troops for decrease of #ability# damage."
60095	"Blessing"
60096	"When the starting the battle, increase #ability# moving speed. This effect last during battle."
60097	"Speed Troops"
60098	"Increase #ability# moving speed of the Flame Knights."
60099	"A sharp spear"
60100	"Increase #ability# damage of Flame Knights."
60101	"Capture "
60102	"If you remove all the enemy, Increase moving speed for #duration#s."
60103	"Critical first attack"
60104	"Increase critical attack possibility #ability#% for the first attack."
60105	"Rush"
60106	"When you pass the close troops, decrease #ability# moving speed. When the troops move, 5% damage to enemy."
60107	"Flame knights"
60108	"Holy Ghost coiled Flame knights, when the knights moving, #ability# damage is added to enemy."
60109	"Courage"
60110	"Increase #ability# damage of one troop."
60111	"Flame spear"
60112	"Additional #ability# damage to Ancient Ent."
60113	"Trample"
60114	"Additional #ability# damage to holy Spearman, Arcane snifer, Flame Knights."
60115	"impose hands Healing"
60116	"Increase troop's vitality, every seconds"
60117	"Flawy spear"
60118	"If the moving speed is fast, increase your damage."
60119	"Sacred flame"
60120	"Knights's spear caught flame in the Holy Ghost fire and additional #ability# damage to enemy."
60121	"Strong axe"
60122	"Increase #ability# damage of Minotaur Hell."
60123	"Strong vitality"
60124	"Increase #ability# vitality of Minotaur Hell."
60125	"Sharp axe"
60126	"Increase #ability# Critical damage of Minotaur Hell"
60127	"Dash"
60128	"Dash to the enemy and knocked them for #duration#s."
60129	"Roar"
60130	"#prob# roar for enemies to attack Minotaur Hell and decrease their attack speed for #duration#s."
60131	"Swing"
60132	"When you attack the enemy, #ability# damage to them with probability #prob#."
60133	"Shock wave"
60134	"When you dash to enemy, the shock wave #ability# damage to enemy."
60135	"Hellfire protection"
60136	"Envelop oneself in hellfire and #ability# damage to enemy."
60137	"Berserk"
60138	"If the vitality below a certain level, Increase #ability# damage by anger state."
60139	"Huge axe"
60140	"#ability# damage to the enemy who fainted. "
60141	"Cow Bell"
60142	"Decrease #ability# damage of the enemy for #duration#s."
60143	"Mad cow"
60144	"When the troops became mad state, Increase #ability# moving speed and attack speed."
60145	"Grow"
60146	"If the troops are beaten, grow strong and body."
60147	"Milk explosion"
60148	"When Minotaur Hell die, explode corrupted milk and #ability damage to their damage."
60149	"Laser Upgrade"
60150	"Increase #ability# damage by laser's high temperature. "
60151	"Heat loss "
60152	"The nearer the target, Increase damage."
60153	"Increase moving speed."
60154	"Flame hole"
60155	"The laser left a flame hole and #ability# damage to enemy."
60156	"Flame storm"
60157	"The enemy who was shot laser, moving speed slowed down for #duration#s."
60158	"Sight Upgrade"
60159	"Laser's range lengthen."
60160	"concentration"
60161	"When the troops close attack, don't miss the target with probability #prob#."
60162	"Burn"
60163	"When attacked by laser, they receive a burn and the #ability# damage is added to them. This effect lasts for #duration#s."
60164	"Increase vitality"
60165	"Eye of death"
60166	"When you attack the enemy by laser, you can aim them and #ability# standoff attack damage is added to them. "
60167	"Inferno"
60168	"Change laser with inferno and increase #ability# damage."
60169	"Metal melting"
60170	"They melts Mithril by hot beam and the #ability# damage is added to holy Spearman. This attack ignores defense."
60171	"Double laser"
60172	"The forked beam attack the two target with #prob# probability."
60173	"Small eye recall"
60174	"When they crush all their enemies, recall the eye and the #ability# damage is added to them. If the eye attacked, that is destroyed.  "
60175	"Sharp teeth"
60176	"Dash"
60177	"Increase #ability# moving speed of Big Lycan."
60178	"Shrewd attack "
60179	"Increase #ability# moving speed of Big Lycan."
60180	"Hunting instinct"
60181	"Increase #ability# attack speed, when attacking holy Spearman, Arcane snifer, Flame Knights."
60182	"Adrenalin"
60183	"Moving speed doubles with #prob#probability when you attack the enemy."
60184	"Vile attack"
60185	"First they can damage bleeding enemy and the #ability# damage is added to them."
60186	"Disregard"
60187	"They attack the ignored enemy until it dies with #prob# probability. "
60188	"Mad dog"
60189	"#prob#probability, become mad dog state when they catch the target. They ignores moving speed hindrance effect."
60190	"Deadly"
60191	"During the attack the enemy, all attack is critical attack damage with #prob# probability for #duration#s."
60192	"Poison claw"
60193	"The enemies are infected by Big Lycan's poison claw. "
60194	"Rabies"
60195	"They can't identify friend or foe by Rabies state of Big Lycan with #prob# probability."
60196	"Immortal blood"
60197	"When they receive damage of death then continue attack enemy with #prob# probability for #duration#s"
60198	"Vampire"
60199	"They take the #ability# vitality because the amount of damage is the same with the amount of attack."
60200	"Contagion"
60201	"If they die on Rabies state, remain disease cloud and #ability# damage them."
60202	"Tight skin"
60203	"Increase #ability# defense of Magma Golem."
60204	"Increase Magma Golem's vitality"
60205	"Earthquake"
60206	"When you attack the enemy, #ability# wide area damage to them by Earthquake with probability #prob#."
60207	"Provocation"
60208	"When they provoke the enemy, the enemy attack Magma Golem with probability #prob#."
60209	"Mental confusion"
60210	"Decrease #ability# moving speed and attack speed by Earthquake."
60211	"Skin upgrade"
60212	"Increase #ability# defense of Magma Golem in provocation."
60213	"Wide area provocation"
60214	"When you attack the enemy, you can induce enemy's attack with probability #prob#."
60215	"Lava fragment"
60216	"Whenever Magma Golem is attacked by enemy, the magma fragment #ability# damage them."
60217	"Shock mitigation"
60218	"Decrease #ability# damage of Magma Golem."
60219	"Sacrifice"
60220	"Our troops under attack by enemy then Magma Golem accept their attack."
60221	"Suicide bombing"
60222	"When their vitality became under 10%, prepare for suicide bombing. If they bomb out, #ability# damage enemy."
60223	"split"
60224	"If Magma Golem die, that splits into two. If that levels rise, mini magma golem's vitality could increase."
60225	"Protection "
60226	"When the battle start, they protect long distance troop by Magma Golem's bark."
60227	"Solid rock"
60228	"Increase #ability# damage of Ancient Ent."
60229	"Solid bark"
60230	"Ancient Ent's defense and vitality increase #ability#. "
60231	"Increase #ability# attack speed of Ancient Ent."
60232	"Entangle"
60233	"Wind ankle by root, reduce #ability# moving speed."
60234	"Grudge "
60235	"That caused damage to large target 15%, middle target 30%. Decrease 20% damage small target."
60236	"Bounce"
60237	"The #ability# damage is added to enemy by bounce rock."
60238	"Arcane snifer concealment"
60239	"Our trooops hide state of self by Ancient Ent's leap."
60240	"Implant root"
60241	"You can shoot farther away. But our troops are defenceless against close range attack."
60242	"Adamantium rock"
60243	"Shoot the Adamantium rock instead of rock, the #ability# damage is added to them."
60244	"Strong bounce"
60245	"The rock is highly malleable."
60246	"Phytoncide"
60247	"Our troops receive the damage #ability#, attack speed #ability#, vitality rise #ability# around at Ancient Ent. They are immune to poison."
60248	"Blocking view"
60249	"Decrease #ability# damage of our troops by opulent foliag from long distance attack."
60250	"Huge rock"
60251	"Ranged rock attack is the splash damage."
60252	"Photosynthesis"
60253	"As they grow larger and recover vitality in #ability# regeneration time. The close damage increase 1%."
60254	"Cordyceps"
60255	"If kill small unit, they changes tree Evil Monster and attack the enemy."
60256	"Increase #ability# attack speed of Fallen Angel."
60257	"Pain"
60258	"When they start battle, the magician who cast the pain spell on enemy and the #ability# damage is added to them."
60259	"Increase #ability# damage of Fallen Angel."
60260	"Rot"
60261	"Decay the enemy's skin and the #ability# damage is added to them."
60262	"Grasp weak point"
60263	"Increase #ability# critical damage because enemy's weakness."
60264	"Corruption"
60265	"Increase critical damage #ability2# instead of decrease #ability1# defense power."
60266	"Strategy"
60267	"When the two fallen Angel's troops attack large target, increase #ability# critical attack damage."
60268	"Harassment"
60269	"Avoidance rate is #ability# from small and middle unit's close attack."
60270	"Hold grudges"
60271	"If the Fallen Angel die, decrease #ability# vitality of attacker. That is not disappeared."
60272	"When they start battle, enemies are wandering in fear for #duration#."
60273	"Punishment"
60274	"Increase #ability# damage to large target."
60275	"Destruction "
60276	"Increase #ability# damage to midsize target."
60277	"When they attack enemy, sweep the enemy and #ability# damage them."
60278	"Brand"
60279	"When they start battle, they brands enemy and increase critical #ability# damage."
60280	"Blind"
60281	"When they start battle, they are blocking an enemy's troop sight. This effect lasts for battle time."
60282	"Increase #ability# moving speed of Cyclope."
60283	"Increase #ability# vitality."
60284	"Increase #ability#moving speed."
60285	"Increase #ability# damage of Big Lycan."
60500	"vitality Upgrade"
60501	"Increase #ability# strenght of our troops."
60502	"Close tactic veteran"
60503	"Increase #ability# moving speed of close combat troops."
60504	"Quick attack"
60505	"Increase #ability# attack speed of our troops."
60506	"Veteran archer"
60507	"Increase #ability# attack speed of Arcane snifer."
60508	"Information of scout"
60509	"Increase #ability# damage to all enemies"
60510	"Ranged combat strategy"
60511	"Decrease #ability# skill reuse time of long distance hero."
60512	"Stamina Upgrade"
60513	"Increase #ability# moving speed of our troops."
60514	"Horseback riding expert"
60515	"Increase #ability# Damage of Flame Knights."



//     유저대상 메세지(UI)
80000	"Hero"
80001	"Skill"
80002	"Item"
80003	"Select Unit"
80004	"Barrack"
80005	"Select"
80006	"Close"
80007	"Please select soldier."
80008	"Use"
80009	"OK"
80010	"Level up"
80011	"EXP increase"
80012	"Cash"
80013	"Loot"
80014	"Etc"
80015	"Sell"
80016	"Legion forming"
80017	"Decision"
80018	"Skill Level up"
80019	"Expansion"
80020	"Troops Level up"
80021	"Retention quantity %d"
80022	"You want to troop's level up by %s Item?"
80023	"You want to hero skill level up by %s scroll?"
80024	"Troops Level up!"
80025	"Leader"
80026	"Decision"
80027	"Trader"
80028	"Trade"
80029	"Valuables shop"
80030	"Weapon trader"
80031	"All"
80032	"Nomal hero\n Employment "
80033	"Epic hero\n Employment "
80034	"Hire 1~4 grade hero using gold %d."
80035	"Hire 3~4 grade ramdom hero using gold %d or jewel %d."
80036	"Hire"
80037	"Damage"
80038	"Range"
80039	"Defense"
80040	"HP"
80041	"Attack speed"
80042	"Movig speed"
80043	"Buy"
80044	"Success hire"
80045	"Kick"
80046	"Soldier level up "
80047	"Lv%d %s"
80048	"Resource quotation"
80049	"Research"
80050	"Employment"
80051	"Storage"
80052	"Market"
80053	"Hero employment"
80054	"you want to hire hero by %s %d?"
80055	"Gold."
80056	"Not enough gold(need %d gold.)"
80057	"Not enough gold(need %d gold or jewel %d.)"
80058	"1 piece : %.2g"
80059	"Extend storage using the key. You want it?"
80060	"Not enough your key. You want to extend sapce by %d cash?"
80061	"Troops damage"
80062	"I'm trader and wander world. I want to trade resource. I'll pay you enough."
80063	"Did you find item?"
80064	"Equipment"
80065	"New arrangement"
80066	"You want new arrangement by Item?"
80067	"Purchase it?"
80068	"Not enough your Item. You want want new arrangement by %d cash?"
80069	"Your gold is not enough. You want to buy %d gold as a cash %d?"
80070	"Purchase "
80071	"Really purchase it?"
80072	"Letter box"
80073	"Social"
80074	"Option"
80075	"Rank"
80076	"Get"
80077	"Title"
80078	"Contents"
80079	"Sound off"
80080	"Select language"
80081	"Register account"
80082	"Reject invitation"
80083	"Before"
80084	"Next"
80085	"Select helmet."
80086	"Equip"
80087	"Select armor"
80088	"Select gloves"
80089	"Select shoes"
80090	"Select accessory"
80091	"No mail"
80092	"Decision"
80093	"Need %d level"
80094	"No skill"
80095	"Generation"
80096	"%d person"
80097	"Can't join"
80098	"Union name"
80099	"Condition"
80100	"Search"
80101	"No search result"
80102	"Union member"
80103	"Grade"
80104	"Login date"
80105	"Member management"
80106	"Union management"
80107	"Union instruction"
80108	"Edit"
80109	"Kick"
80110	"Fighting power %d "
80111	"Reder point %d "
80112	"Hero's job %s"
80113	"Join"
80114	"Auto approval"
80115	"Reject"
80116	"Cancel join"
80117	"Enter the union contents"
80118	"%s, you can't join now."
80119	"Please try at a later time."
80120	"Kick out %s?"
80121	"The %s  union's member is full."
80122	"Check repetition"
80123	"Founder of union"
80124	"Join rejected"
80125	"Raid"
80126	"You already join a union and can't found that."
80127	"Ranking"
80128	"User name"
80129	"Point"
80130	"Call immediately"
80131	"Remaining time"
80132	"Call"
80133	"You want to call trader by Item?"
80134	"Not enough Item. You want to call immediately by 3cash?"
80135	"Do you want to deal?"
80136	"Little cash"
80137	"Cash"
80138	"Plenty cash"
80139	"Substantially cash"
80140	"Not enough cash."
80141	"Not enough cash"
80142	"Registration"
80143	"Cancel"
80144	"Email"
80145	"Password"
80146	"Password Confirm "
80147	"This email has already been used or the password you typed do not match."
80148	"You want to call immediately by Item?"
80149	"Not enough Item. You want to call immediately by %d cash?"
80150	"Not enough Item and cash. Please purchase it."
80151	"Trade resource"
80152	"The item is sold out. Please arrange Item."
80153	"The name is already being used."
80154	"Please enter a game name."
80155	"Monthly flat-rate cash"
80156	"You already join a union."
80157	"Please enter union's contents"
80158	"%d grade"
80159	"Joining"
80160	"Approval"
80161	"Rejection"
80162	"Member name"
80163	"Resource"
80164	"Hourly output"
80165	"Secession"
80166	"The storage reach the limit."
80167	"You want to Kick hero and get Clan's exp book? If you Kick hero, you can't get this no more."
80168	"Please join a union. You can reid in union."
80169	"Not enough gold."
80170	"Other device is connected and you cannot connect to this server."
80171	"You have to tidy the storage then you can join a battle."
80172	"Account linkage"
80173	"This account is not exist or wrong password."
80174	"The game is shutdown. Please restart the game."
80175	"If you want battle, you have to arrange one or more heroes."
80176	"Union interpretation"
80193	"남은 시간 %02d:%02d:%02d"
80208	"남은 시간 %02d:%02d"
