2016	"Experience point:%d"
2019	"Required Hero level"
2031	"Sudden attack of enemy Monarch!"
2034	"Attack by other player! If you are defeated then you will lose all of your acquired sulfur."
2100	"Minimum"
2104	"Passive skill"
2119	"Gold coin is not enough. Do you want to use Gem instead?"
2120	"Resource is not enough. Do you want to use Gem instead?"
2133	"Training camp"
2148	"White crow troop7"
2209	"Do you want to use Gem for your lacking alliance point %d?"  
2211	"%s purchase completed."
2217	"Acquired Reward"
2228	"Daily Battle field"
2229	"Maximum"
2230	"Day"
2231	"Hour"
2232	"Minute"
2233	"Second"
2234	"Level increased!"
2235	"Revitalize to Hero grade 3level(★★★)." 
2236	"Battle field of Hero"
2237	"Bonus Conquest point(★)"
2238	"Re-entering remaining time"
2239	"Open the previous area first"
2240	"Acting power AP is low"
2241	"Can use by opening %dlevel of %s area." 
2242	"%s increased"
2243	"%s decreased"
2244	"Changing soldier"
2245	"send crash dump"
2246	"Plunder record"
2247	"Quest"
2248	"Acquired sulfur"
2249	"Hero level training"
2250	"Hero troops training"
2251	"Hero skill training"
2252	"Investing amount of training expense"
2253	"Final training expense"
2254	"Next level"
2255	"Training time"
2256	"Remaining training time"
2257	"Troops level"
2258	"Skill level"
2259	"Ability point change amount"
2260	"Congratulation!"
2261	"Mission accomplished!"
2262	"Medal is low. Do you want to purhase it by gem?(not materialized)"
2263	"Unable to identify other player"
2264	"Defending"
2265	"Current reward"
2266	"Production resources"
2267	"Minute"
2268	"Rewarding next win"
2269	"Rewarding %dconsecutive victories(acquired)"
2270	"Welcome!"
2271	"Total played time"
2272	"Type the message which can be shown to other player."
2273	"Win"
2274	"Lose"
2275	"Resetting characteristics"
2276	"Remaining points"
2277	"Number of remaining unlocking"
2278	"Do you want to use characteristics point one?"
2279	"Do you want to %dpoint back by resetting the [%s]of characteristcs tree? Required Gold coin:%s"
2280	"This Hero cannot be resetted anymore. If you want resetting you need relevant item."
2281	"Trader returning"
2282	"under training"
2283	"Cannot expand more."
2284	"Please touch"
2285	"2016 Gemtree. All right reserved."
2286	"Guild coin"
2287	"Unlock"
2288	"Failed to item purchase. Please try again later. Code:"
5005	"Accomplish level#what#."
5006	"Explore the #what# area."
5007	"Kill the #what#."
5008	"Scout the #what#."
5009	"Visit the #what#."
5010	"Kill the #what#."
5011	"Attack the #what#."
5012	"Scout the #what#."
5013	"Visit the #what#."
5014	"Acquired the #what# hero."
5015	"Shoot the #what# dead."
5016	"'#what#' mission accomplished."
5017	"Be succeed on defeding main castle."
5018	"Acquire the #what#."
5019	"Possess the #what#."
5020	"Acquire the #what#."
5021	"Possess the #what#."
5022	"Conquer the #what#."
5023	"Acquire star(★)."
5039	"Complete the hero training immediately."
5043	"Hire the high rank hero to hero barrack."
5074	"Enemy troop"
5077	"Perform the characteristics research."
5078	"Release the lock for new unit."
5079	"Visiting trader and accomplished the resource trading."
5080	"Visiting arms dealer and purchased item."
5081	"Visiting valuables shop and purchase gem."
5083	"Hiring hero at the Hero barrack."
5084	"Summon hero with soul stone."
5085	"Promote hero with collecting soul stones."
5086	"Guildraid final win."
5096	"Kill the enemy forces around the castle."
5099	"Control troop"
5100	"Attain the hero level #what#"
5101	"Attain the hero troop level #what#"
5102	"Attain hero skill level #what#"
5103	"#Battle starts with what#."
5104	"Acquiring new hero"
10008	"Snake"
10160	"Bruinhildai"
10161	"Preyia"
10162	"Malvin"
10163	"Becky"
10164	"Jed"
10218	"Percival"
10219	"Tristan"
10220	"Kay"
10221	"Beddybeer"
15040	"Den of beast brotherhood"
15095	"Battle field of Hero"
15096	"Savage plunderer"
15097	"Assassin troop"
15098	"The Empire 6th corps"
15099	"The Red Rock thieves"
15100	"The Empire 5th corps"
15101	"The Empire 8th corps"
15102	"The Empire 11th corps"
20260	"The group of thieves called the Beast brotherhood is attacking villagers in this area. Destroy the their den completely and bring the peace back to the village."
20316	"Acquire the Gemstone mine. If you can take up the mine then you can provide a large amount of gemstone stably."
20398	"Scoute Gemstone mine"
20399	"It is said that under the south side of mountain range there is mine where is producing Gemstones. Scoute that area."
20400	"Hero challenges to battle field"
20401	"You can get Heros soul stone little by little in daily at the Battle field of hero. Clear the Battle field of Hero stage five."
20402	"Win at the Hero battle field stage five"
20403	"The criminals who is expelled from the Empire has organized their own forces in this Red Rock Mountain. They are keep attacking and damaging the Sulfur mine. Defeat these criminals completely."
20404	"Destroy Red Rock theives"
25310	"Find Hero traing camp"
25324	"Hero training"
25325	"Hero skill training"
25326	"Hero troop training"
25330	"Gem purchased"
25334	"When you are at the level nine, you have to recruit one more Hero. You are maybe short of more money. Need to be ready by collecting resources. Acquire necessary resources. One of the Empire troops should be have this resource."
25340	"Kill the enemy force"
25343	"Kill the chief gatekeeper"
25344	"Collecting star(temporarily)"
25345	"Troop control"
25346	"Learn mannual control for the troop during the battle."
25347	"Check the weak and strong points between troops"
25348	"On the battle ready screen, choose the same side army then check troops who has more strong characteristics."
25349	"Touch the same side army on the battle ready screen."
25350	"Destroy the Empire troop"
25351	"The empire troops are getting increased around area. You cannot guarantee the security for this area unless you destroy the Empire troops."
25352	"Recruiting new Hero"
25353	"As you become level nine, you have one more troop slot so you can send total five troops to the battle. Include new Hero to corps after you recruit one from Hero barrack."
25354	"Visit the Valuables shop"
25355	"Gem is the best when it is urgent. Visit the Valuables shop who sells gem. the shop is in market palce."
25356	"The first 지름"
25357	"The Monarch has to grow faster than others. Cannot survive if you lose in competition!. Try to purchse Gem. Gem can be purchased at the Valuables shop in the market place."
25358	"Recruiting high rank Hero"
25359	"Collecting Gem and recruit high rank Hero from Hero barrack."
25360	"Skill traing"
25361	"Train the Hero skill to #param#level. Any Hero will be fine."
25362	"Soldier characteristics research"
25363	"Perform soldier characteristics research at the research center. It can be any Hero or any soldier."
25364	"Troop training"
25365	"Train the Hero troop to #param#level. Any Hero will be fine."
25366	"Level training"
25367	"Train the Hero to #param#level. any Hero will be fine."
25368	"Guildraid challenge"
25369	"Attack Empire city Ravis. This is the first confronting Empire city. But it is impossible for Monarch alone. Attack the city together with Guildes."
25370	"Guildraid wins"
25371	"Attack Empire city Ravis then acquire the final winning."
25372	"Attack transportation troop who transports Sulfur in Valcanic zone and acquire Sulfur."
25373	"Training completed immediately"
25374	"Even though Hero is under taining, remaining training time will be cleared and training can be completed by paying little amount of Gold coin. Perform the training immediate complete. It can be any training."
25375	"Attack Daily battle field"
25376	"Found Daily battle field. Can challenge five times in daily, and daily reward is defferent. You can restore any short resource in the daily battle field. use it everyday."
25377	"Secure new unit soldier"
25378	"If you want to perform the various tactics than battle moment, you need new monster soldier. Unlock the level 9 zone and release the new unit soldier."
25384	"Change soldier"
25385	"Now you can change hero or soldier before the battle. Press <change soldier> on the line up screen before the battle."
25386	"Attempt changing soldier"
25387	"Collecting Medal"
25388	"You can get the very rare Heros who have not known to world through market Arms dealer. But the Arm dealer wants to change with your Medal. Collect the Medal by winning at the savage base. And bring the Medal to the Arms dealer then purchase Hero sould stone."
25389	"Kill the General of the Empire corps"
25390	"The Empire 5th corps is stationed at level 9 zone. If you defeat them then Medius zone forces will come to #nick#. Win the battle and kill the General of corps."
25391	"Found the Empire 8th corps at the level 12 zone! The safety of Gemstone mine cannot be guaranteed unless you destroy them.  Kill the General of corps Tristan for victory."
25392	"Found the Empire 6th corps! You must destroy them to enter the Sulfur zone. Win the battle and kill the General of corps Kay."
25393	"Need to destroy the Empire 11th corps. If you defeat them you can enter to the Mandrake field where you can get lots of Mandrake. The leader of 11th corps is Beddybeer who is brother of Kay the General of 6th corps. He wants revenge for his brother. Kill the General Baddybeer."
25394	"Summon the Hero using soul stone"
25395	"You can use Hero barrack to get Hero but also you can summon the Hero by collecting 10 soul stones. Summon the Hero by collecting soul stone of Hero you have not possessed yet. The soul stone can be received from <Hero battle field> or other Monarch castle, or the Arms dealer."
25396	"Promote Hero"
25397	"Hero rank is shown by number of star(★). If you want to promote the Hero, you need to collect the Hero soul stone for required number. Promote one star(★)Hero to two star(★★)Hero."
25398	"We need more capable Heros. Promote 2 star(★★)Hero to 3 star(★★★)Hero. When the Hero becomes 3 star Hero then Hero can use Passive skill."
25399	"Monarch's Hero is getting stronger. Promote the Hero to 4 star(★★★★). They will raise the bloodwind in the Battle field. "
25400	"As you become level 12, you have one more troop slot and you can send total 6 troops to batle field. Recruit a Hero. You can use any method."
25401	"Request from the Royal wizards that they need large amount of Mandrake. Seek and give mandrake."
25402	"Empire army is everywhere. You should destroy them first."
27001	"Found a small size of Empire troop is stationed in and around mountain Medius. The troop's size is not big but it is better for us not to be discovered by them. Kill them."
27013	"Destroy the Empire troops around the castle."
27310	"Need training camp to do the Hero level and skill training. Search the training camp in Medius ravine."
27321	"In order to demonstrate true power, hero needs leadership for unit troop under the his command. Start training for Hero's troop."
27324	"Training camp is opened. Training camp is the place to increase level or train skill by investing Gold coins to Hero. Start Hero level training."
27325	"Gold coin is alot short. Now you can get Gemstone/Sulfur/Mandrake whenever you destroy enemy troop, you can sell those resources much expensive than wood or metal. You can find what kind of resource you can get by scouting enemy troop. If the resource is not what you want then you can get Mandrake resource when you defeat them and reappear. When you complete it, exchange to Gold coin from Trader."
27330	"Gem is important resource can help to use various high function. It is in sale at the Valuables shop and visit the shop and buy the Gem."
27340	"There are still many remained enemy forces around us. Savage tribe is remained and the Empire armies are still seen occasionally. To be secured, we need to destroy them."
27342	"Empire troop is guarding the main gate. This is major trading road so you must destroy them."
27344	"(Temporarily)Get reward by taking the star from your enemy."
45500	"You can exchange with rare soul stone if you bring it to the Arms dealer. You can get it from Savage main base."
45522	"It increases Hero experience point."
55000	"Allocate Archer troop to behind of Spear troop. Longer to survive Archer troop gives better winning chance."
55008	"Before the battle, try to change your Hero or soldier compare to enemy's format."
55009	"If you have gold coin, keep train the hero. This is easy way to grow your hero without taking mush time."
55010	"Damage level is increased by 25% when Defend unit (Spear soldier, Minotaur, Golem) gives damage to Speed unit (Knight, Lycan, Fallen angel)."
55011	"Damage level is increased by 25% when Long distance unit(Archer, Cyclops, Tree spirit) gives damage to Defend unit (Spear soldier, Minotaur, Golem)."
55012	"Damage level is increased by 25% when Speed unit (Knight, Lycan, Fallen angel) gives damage to Long distance unit(Archer, Cyclops, Tree spirit)."
55013	"Damage level is increased by 25% when Small unit (Spear soldier. Archer, Knight)gives damage to Large unit(Golem, Tree spirit, Fallen anger)."
55014	"Damage level increased by 25% when Mid unit(Minotraur, Lycan, Cyclops) gives damage to  Small unit (Spear soldier. Archer, Knight)."
55015	"Damage level is increased by 25% when Large unit(Golem, Tree spirit, Fallen anger) gives damage to Mid unit(Minotraur, Lycan, Cyclops)."
55017	"Damage levelis decreased by 25% when Defend unit (Spear soldier, Minotaur, Golem) gets attack from Speed unit (Knight, Lycan, Fallen angel)."
55018	"Damage level is decreased by 25% when Long distance unit(Archer, Cyclops, Tree spirit) gets attack from Defend unit (Spear soldier, Minotaur, Golem)."
55019	"Damage levelis decreased by 25% when Speed unit (Knight, Lycan, Fallen angel) gets attack from Long distance unit(Archer, Cyclops, Tree spirit)."
55020	"Damage level is decreased by 25% when Small unit (Spear soldier. Archer, Knight) gets attack from Large unit(Golem, Tree spirit, Fallen anger)."
55021	"Damage levelis decreased by 25% when Mid unit(Minotraur, Lycan, Cyclops) gets attack from Small unit (Spear soldier. Archer, Knight)."
55022	"Damage levelis decreased by 25% when Large unit(Golem, Tree spirit, Fallen anger) gets attack from Mid unit(Minotraur, Lycan, Cyclops)."
55023	"The strategy can be changed depend on what skill Hero uses."
55024	"Increase star level by collecting Hero soul stone."
55500	"The color of mark on the spot means level of difficulty. Level3 (yelow)spot means having similar battle power like yours."
55504	"If you win by more than 2 starts(★★★)then conquest point bonus will be applied to get more resources."
55505	"At the Battle field of Hero, you can raise star level or recruit new Hero by collecting Heros soul stone."
55506	"Daily battle field has different rewatd resource in daily. And when level is increased, amout of reward is also increased."
55507	"If you want harder and lager reward battle then you need to open the new zone."
55510	"if you open 9,12,15,18,21,24 level zone you can unlock the new unit soldier."
55511	"At the Arms dealer shop in the market, you can get a new hero who is only sold in there."
55513	"Passive skill of  Hero who is assigned as the General of corps can be applied to all troops."
55514	"Getting higher level zone, stronger opponent is appeared."
55516	"You can get powerful hero who is only availble at the guild store by collecting Guild coin from Guildraid."
55517	"You can raise start level by collecting Soul stone."
55518	"When you expand the Training camp slot, you can train many Hero at the same time."
55519	"If you destroy enemy resource troop in the battle, you can gent certain amount of resource when you defeat them.  Location of resource troop can be known before battle allocation."
60009	"Throw huge fireball to enemy troop and give #ability#damage on troop attack power to all enemy troops in range of explosion."
60012	"Protect magnetic field"
60013	"Decrease all the damage to troop for #duration#between second #ability# by covering up the troop with strong magnetic field."
60018	"Blow of soul"
60028	"Paralysis arrow"
60029	"Shoot the arrow which has neural paralysis material and damage #ability1# and make paralysis state for #duration2# seconds."
60030	"Sight of Eagle"
60031	"Have the sight of eagle for #duration#seconds then your range will be increased by #ability#meters."
60191	"At the attack, excercise with #prob#probability and attack for #duration#seconds then it will give fatal damage"
60272	"At the beginning, pick one enemy troop and terrorize them. The terrorized enemy cannot make any attack and wonder for #duration#seconds."
60516	"Steel arrow"
60619	"Giving #ability#damage by shoot the arrow which gives unhealing wound and give ability2#damage for #duration2#seconds."
60620	"Sight  blow"
60622	"Close combat"
60623	"You can fight at the close combat because #ability# long distance attack power will be applied."
60624	"Assassin"
60625	"Give #ability#damage of attack power and kill instantly by 10% of probability by shooting strong blow of arrow to hero in target troop."
60626	"aim and shoot"
60627	"Shoot arrow which can hit the mark with deadly blow for #duration#seconds and ability#probability"
60628	"Fast retreat"
60629	"When troop gets close attack within #duration#seconds, it can teleport to random location in battle field."
60630	"Fast load"
60631	"Attack speed of troop will be #ability#faster for #duration#seconds."
60632	"Tornado sword"
60633	"Give #ability1#damage to around enemies with strong tornado attack. And whoever gets the damage, its attack power will be decreased by #ability2#."
60634	"Flame armor"
60635	"Flame armor will cover the body and give damage to around enemies for #duration#seconds and give #ability# flamedamage."
60636	"Sword of wind"
60637	"This is swordmanship which contain power of wind will give #ability1# damage and decrease attack power by #ability2# with slow enemy's movement."
60638	"Cold tent"
60639	"Decrease the flaming damage #ability1# for #duration# by covering troop and freeze around enemies so that decrease their moving speed #ability2#."
60640	"Thunderbolt attack"
60641	"Give #ability#damage by attacking enemy using strong thunderbolt power."
60642	"Giant hunter"
60643	"Give additional #ability# damage by temporarily collecting rage when you confront to large unit ."
60644	"Energy tent"
60645	"Will be immune to all damage for#duration# by shock energy abording tent which covers the troop."
60646	"Fast march"
60647	"Increase troop moving speed by#ability# for #duration#seconds."
60648	"Regenerate fo pain"
60649	"Change pain to life energy. Restore the strength by #ability# of total strength."
60650	"Shield defend"
60651	"Decrease damage by #ability# from enemy'slong distance attack by marching with shield."
60652	"Guerrilla attack"
60653	"Decrease damage caused of close combat by #ability for #duration#seconds."
60654	"Preemptive attack"
60655	"With fast preemptive attack, give damage by #ability# to smaill size troop."
60656	"Terrorized attack"
60657	"Give damage by #ability# and terorize to enemy troop."
60658	"Mean ambush"
60659	"Give damage to opponent by #ability1#  and make it bleed for #duration2#."
60660	"Deadly rush"
60661	"Rush with one lethal blow make all attack as fatal bow for #duration#."
60662	"Losing sight blow"
60663	" At the attack, take enemy's sight by 20% probability the decrease accuracy rate for #duration#seconds."
60664	"Glorious march"
60665	"Glorious troop's confidence becomes temporarily increase so that attack power #ability1# and attack speed #ability2# will be increased."
60666	"Threat"
60667	"Enemy troop who feel the threat will lose their confidence so that attack power #ability1# and attack speed #ability2# will be decreased."
70027	"Show level of hero. More star makes better ability. Can promote hero with hero's soul stone."
70028	"If a Hero becomes leader of troop then this passive ability will apply to all army."
70029	"Therefore it is immportant strategy who will become leader."
70033	"Combat skill using by a hero. There are two types of skills which are active skill and passive skill."
70034	"Active skill is the skill can use directly during the battle. If there is no special direct order from monarch, then generals can use it by themselves."
70035	"Passive skill is the ability can be always activated without specific control. But this ability can be activated when hero becomes level3(★★★)."
70055	"Now do you know what to do? Then keep perform your mission"
70086	"First, choose the skill you want then unlock it."
70087	"After you unlock it, then touch the +button and start to study."
70088	"Choose same side troop then touch to random location or enemy troop."
70089	"You received star conquest quest."
70101	"First one time is free so try it."
70104	"You found the Empire 5th corps."
70105	"It will not be an easy fight because this is not the same main troop as before."
70106	"Base on scoute result, the General Percival's archer troop of both sides looks threatening. It is better to make them powerless first."
70109	"I am the General of the Empire 5th troop, Percival."
70110	"You have to pass me before pass the south mountain range."
70111	"Now let's do it!"
70116	"Welcome. You are looking for strong friends."
70129	"When you are in Hero level, press this."
70135	"Now you have army base camp, you need to train your armies."
70136	"But soon other player will attack and take over this castle."
70137	"And if Monarch conquer this castle then automatically you can collect resource tax from the castle. But if you loose then the castle tax will be decreased in large amount."
70138	"Therefore you have to take the castle back quickly when you lose it."
70139	"This is Empire 8th corps who defend mine zone."
70140	"If you can block Gemstone which is provided to Empire then you can give major damage to Empire army training."
70141	"The General of 8th corps called Tristan. He is known as best archer. Cyclops troop is located at the both sides of general troop."
70142	"This Cyclops troop will be threatening to our spear troop, so it is better to destroy Cyclops troop first."
70143	"I am the General of the Empire 8th corps, Tristan. Do you come to take this Gemstone mine?"
70144	"Many Monarchs got killed by my arrows for covetting here. I will make a hole to your head!"
70167	"Hero can automatically receive experience point by battling, but if hero use training camp then can receive additional experience point by using gold coin and investing time."
70168	"In other words, if you have Gold coin you can raise Hero level more quickly. So let's start training"
70170	"You can have training for increasing Hero level in here."
70171	"You need little bit of money and time for training. "
70172	"By pressing +,- button, you can choose amount of money and training time you want to invest and press training start then training will begin."
70173	"When the training is begin you have to wait until the training is over, but if you want to finish it earlier then you can do it by paying Gold coin."
70174	"If you have enough gold coin then it is better way to finish the training earlier. Becasue we need to be stronger quickly."
70175	"It is same for skill upgrade or troop upgrade."
70176	"Now press +,-button and start the training."
70177	"Empire main force is encamping at entrance of the Sulfur area."
70178	"You must pass this area to acquire a large amount of sulfur. Be ready."
70179	"It is the famous #nick#. How dare you to come to Kay. puhahaha"
70180	"#nick#! Your heroic tale is end here!"
70181	"Empire 11th corps is guarding the way to Mandrake field."
70182	"It will be tough battle. Since most of soldiers are Minotaur, it is better to format the troop favorable to Minotaur."
70183	"Are you the one who killed my brother Kay! I cannot believe that Kay got defeated by such a rookie!"
70184	"We must pay back what we owe! We will pay back with your head!!"
70191	"Mandrake is on wide spread plain level 19 Mandrake farm and it is same."
70192	"You can find about your enemy troop  whether it is advantageous or disadavantgeous to you by selecting one of your troops."
70193	"From now, there will be star point mark on each battle spot."
70194	"This star point tells you how you completely conquest the battle spot."
70195	"When you finish the battle at the given spot, you will receive point with star point.."
70196	"Star point is decided by  <battle time> and <remained strength> of your army after the battle."
70197	"In other words, you will get 3star points when you overwhelmingly win your opponent."
70198	"If you barely win then you only get 1 star point."
70199	"Quest will be completed when gained star points are accumulated collect more than a certain amount."
70200	"Even though this mission is completed, you will keep getting next star point conquest quest. Of course, the reward is getting better"
70201	"Also you will get 100% when you have conquered place with 3 star points of resource after the battle. Otherwise you will get penalty on your conquer."
70202	"If you conquer with 3 star points then star mark will be disappeared."
80012	"Gem"
80034	"Hire 1(★)grade hero. If you are lucky, you can get 2, 3 grade hero."
80035	"Hire 3(★★★)grade hero. If you are lucky you can get 4 garde hero."
80054	"Do you want to hire hero by using %s %s?"
80056	"Gold coin is short.(Need %sgold coin)"
80057	"Gem is short.(Need gem%s)"
80058	"Per 1 : %.0f Gold coin"
80060	"Key is short. Do you want to expand space by using up the Gem %d?"
80068	"Item is short. Do you want to allocate by using Gem %d?"
80069	"Gold coin is short. Do you want to buy %Gold coin item by using Gem %d?"
80088	"Choose weapon."
80134	"Item is short Do you want summon immediately by using Gem3?"
80136	"Less gem"
80137	"Gem"
80138	"More gem"
80139	"Much more gem"
80140	"Gem is short."
80141	"Gem shortage"
80149	"Item is short. Will you call by using Gem %d?"
80150	"Item and gem are short. Purchase it"
80155	"Monthly paid gem"
80167	"Do you want to recorded strategy book which belongs to the Hero by expiring Hero? If you expire the Hero you cannot get it back again."
80190	"Daily battle field"
90001	"Hero level up training is completed"
90002	"Hero troop training is completed"
90003	"Hero skill training is completed"
